<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Factions>
	<!-- 
	MAJOR KINGDOM FACTIONS
	-->
	<!--
	Aserai Emirates
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_6"
	         name="{=l6JtB97p}Banu Atij"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_18"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_6_text}The Banu Atij are without peer in the vast and dusty lands to the south of Calradia that comprise the Nahasa Desert. Unlike many of their kin among the Aserai, they were quick to realize the value of using their nomadic warriors to protect - rather than raid - the merchant caravans crossing the great bronze desert. From their seat of power at the ancient oasis city of Qasira, the caravans of the Banu Atij range far and wide across the continent, bringing vast wealth through the trade of dates, silks and spices. This wealth has brought them great status among the Aserai, and there are few emirs who would deny the summons of the Banu Atij to matters of politics or war."
	         banner_key="11.61.154.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.428.137.0.450.450.764.804.0.0.0.521.137.0.100.100.764.534.0.0.0.144.137.0.300.300.759.734.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_5"
	         name="{=zY2TQC9t}Banu Arbas"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_17"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_5_text}The Banu Arbas, unlike many old and prestigious families of the Nahasa, cannot claim great wealth, fame, or political clout in their line of descent. Instead, they lay claim to a lineage of the finest warriors of the great bronze desert, serving as the vanguard of many an emir’s host. In the years before the tribes of the Aserai settled in great towns along the coast of the Bahr al-Yeshm and around the oases of Calradia’s south, the Banu Arbas were feared as the scourge of any caravans who dared to enter their territory, raiding from the Jabal Ashabi Mountains in the east, to the Jabal Tamar Mountains in the west. Now settled in the lush lands along the Damar River, they have lost none of their potency on the field of battle, and few would dare to face them in the desolate, sandy dunes of their homeland."
	         banner_key="11.61.154.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.428.137.0.450.450.764.804.0.0.0.521.137.0.100.100.764.534.0.0.0.144.137.0.300.300.759.734.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_2"
	         name="{=fvYgmrjG}Banu Sarran"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_3"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_2_text}The Banu Sarran are the rulers of one of the most recent emirates of the Nahasa, though also one of the oldest families of the Nahasa, claiming descent from the legendary Asera himself. In the past centuries, the Banu Sarran fought a series of brutal conflicts with the neighboring Banu Hulyan Emirate, attempting to seize lands off the latter to form their own realm. Ultimately unsuccessful in this, they are widely shunned by the other Aserai emirates as upstarts and violent usurpers, though this is a reputation which they in fact relish. They celebrate their nomadic past in odes and poems on their success in battle over fellow Aserai, or in seducing the other tribes' daughters. This does not endear them to the other peoples of the Nahasa, though they do maintain close ties with the Jawwal - that clan of outcasts who still live the nomadic lifestyle."
	         banner_key="11.156.75.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.223.1.0.454.454.764.764.0.0.359.515.1.0.177.177.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.358.358.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_3"
	         name="{=wFR1ukg9}Banu Qild"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_5"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_3_text}The Banu Qild are renowned across the lands of the Nahasa as a family of dour ascetics, looking down from their desert fastnesses with equal disapproval on both the wealthy and poor of the Aserai. Few who travel to their fortress home of Hubyar return with tales of their hospitality, nor of their charm. However, somehow the Banu Qild have always retained a position of primacy in the politics of the great bronze desert, with more than one ancient Aserai family being ensnared by their cunning. Indeed, there are whispers that they long for days that they might lord over the other families of the Nahasa, uniting the disparate emirates into a single realm, with a Banu Qild at its head."
	         banner_key="11.7.75.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.500.1.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0.309.1.0.300.300.764.654.0.0.-130.427.1.0.300.300.764.844.0.0.0.521.1.0.196.196.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_7"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_7_name}Banu Maluf"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_19"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_7_text}The Banu Maluf are one of the wealthiest among the small emirates that rule over the southern Nahasa Desert, controlling one of the only oases along the caravan routes from the desert interior to the lands of the Darshi Empire to the east. In the days before the Aserai traded the saddle for the luxuries of high walls and perfumed palaces, the Banu Maluf served as the primary guides and protectors of merchants traversing the Nahasa, albeit for a hefty price. That tradition has continued into the present, with riders of the Banu Maluf ranging far and wide across the deserts to ‘remind’ would-be caravaners to pay their dues."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.500.1.0.186.186.764.747.0.0.-89.222.1.0.559.583.764.785.0.0.-180.428.1.0.284.284.764.786.0.0.0.500.1.0.180.180.764.747.0.0.-89.500.1.0.173.173.764.747.0.0.-89.503.1.0.140.140.764.744.0.0.-1.500.1.0.359.359.764.780.0.0.-89"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_8"
	         name="{=o4wKMT9x}Banu Habbab"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_20"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_8_text}The Banu Habbab are one of the least settled of the Aserai emirates, still holding to the old traditions from their nomadic past. Indeed, many visitors to their estates leave with the distinct impression that a stable would be more accommodating. Trading perfumed silks and shaded pleasure gardens for feasting halls adorned with the skins and mounted heads of exotic beasts, the Banu Habbab are often seen associating more with the Bedouin of the Nahasa, than their peers among the Aserai emirs. Placed upon the fringes of society, they are nonetheless one of the most feared peoples of the great bronze desert, and few would dare to challenge their authority on the field."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.428.1.0.510.510.773.781.0.0.0.321.1.0.386.386.766.738.0.0.0.507.1.0.90.90.703.764.0.0.359.507.1.0.90.90.839.761.0.0.359"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_9"
	         name="{=NI1paia1}Banu Ruwaid"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_A9_u"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_9_text}The Banu Ruwaid are one of the more unusual ruling families among the Aserai, claiming descent from an intermarrying of Kannic merchants with Nahasan Bedouin in centuries long past. In the wars between the Kannic city states and the Calradian Empire, the Banu Ruwaid proved invaluable to their kin, leading armies through hidden pathways amid the shifting dunes to ambush the Calradian legions. However, those glories are long past, and the Banu Ruwaid now find themselves ruling a small emirate on the western borderlands of the Aserai, fighting both Calradians and Kannics alike in defense of their realm."
	         banner_key="11.61.154.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.426.137.0.200.200.764.932.0.0.90.156.137.0.300.300.764.763.0.0.0.500.137.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0.521.137.0.200.200.764.521.0.0.90"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_1"
	         name="{=9Y1u2onl}Banu Hulyan"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_1"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_1_text}The Banu Hulyan have the dubious honor of ruling over the western expanses of the Nahasa desert, controlling the key pass in the Jarjara Escarpment through which travellers and merchants move from the Damar River to the Kannic colonies of Quyaz, located on the coast of the Bahr al-Yeshm. This position has brought the Banu Hulyan immense wealth, though their hunger for wealth is tempered by a pragmatism uncommon among the Aserai. Indeed, where some might see an enemy, the Banu Hulyan see only a trading partner who has gone astray. In recent years, their court has become home to an assortment of shamans and prophets, through which the Banu Hulyan hope to win the hearts and minds of the superstitious Aserai. Indeed, there are rumors of a prophet, born to the Banu Hulyan, that might unite the emirates of the great bronze desert - a true sultan for the Banu Asera."
	         banner_key="11.0.0.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.212.1.0.480.480.764.764.0.0.0.521.1.0.150.150.664.844.0.0.0.427.1.0.150.150.864.844.0.0.-90"/>
	<Faction id="clan_aserai_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_4_name}Banu Karama"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_16"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.aserai"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_aserai_4_text}The Banu Karama, like many among the noble families of the Aserai, claim humble origins in the nomadic Bedouin of the Nahasa Desert. Unlike their peers, the Banu Karama represent a bridge between two worlds. In centuries past, the expanding Darshi Empire conquered the eastern lands of the great bronze desert, coming to rule over a number of nomadic tribes in the process. The Banu Karama were one such people, swearing fealty to the Padishah in exchange for lands, titles and wealth. However, with the waning power of the Darshi throwing the eastern Nahasa into chaos, the Banu Karama now find themselves at risk of returning to the obscurity from whence they came - victims of the very shifting sands that brought about their rise."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.2000.2000.764.764.1.0.0.446.1.0.452.452.764.764.0.0.0.518.1.0.100.100.634.864.0.0.0.446.1.0.452.452.764.763.0.0.0.446.1.0.435.435.764.763.0.0.0.411.1.0.175.175.765.767.0.0.359.518.1.0.100.100.894.654.0.0.0.518.1.0.100.100.634.654.0.0.0.518.1.0.100.100.894.874.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Battanian Kingdom
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_battania_2"
	         name="{=zvas3ieB}fen Derngil"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_3"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_2_text}The fen Derngil clan have held the high kingship of the Battanians for generations, having seized power in a bloody coup now lost to time in all but name. They have enforced their rule through the judicious use of violence and diplomacy, being equally comfortable facing their foes on the battlefield and at the negotiating table. From their highland fortress at Dunglanys, the fen Derngil want for little and are threatened by few. Even the Calradian Empire at its height was hard-pressed to usurp their position, instead preferring to attack the Battanian clans along its borders, whose raids on imperial territory have brought the fen Derngil immense wealth in the form of gifts of fealty."
	         banner_key="11.2.2.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.412.13.13.508.508.768.764.0.0.180.504.13.13.95.129.766.731.0.1.3.510.13.13.137.98.658.687.0.1.242.510.13.13.137.97.873.677.0.1.121.510.13.13.137.97.772.866.0.1.2"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_3"
	         name="{=0m0IUnL1}fen Uvain"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_5"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_3_text}The fen Uvain are an ambitious clan who have ruled over a vast estate in the northern extent of the Uchalion Plateau, in a region where the Battanian lands meet the Bay of Varcheg. They are not a martial or particularly charismatic people, preferring to plot from the safety and secrecy afforded by the high walls of their fortress home. Passed over for the high kingship for generations, they resent the current fen Derngil royal house, and have taken to secretly funding a number of clandestine organizations that operate against the interests of the crown. This low cunning has awarded the fen Uvain few friends among the Battanian nobility, though there are equally few who would underestimate their capability in the political arena."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.427.39.0.261.261.764.869.0.0.-1.133.39.0.400.400.764.696.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_battania_1_name}fen Conaill"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_1"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_3_text}The fen Conaill are one of the most ancient Battanian noble clans, having held lands around the fortress of Marunath since the days before Calradios the Great arrived on the continent. They claim to be a mercantile people, though a closer inspection of much of their merchandise reveals it to be suspiciously Calradian in origin - the product of centuries of raiding the unprotected imperial villages along the foothills of the Uchalion Plateau. Despite this wealth, they are widely derided by Battanian society for the harsh tariffs they impose on their clansmen, whose ever-present threat of rebellion places the fen Conaill in a precarious position."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.456.39.0.467.467.764.864.0.0.180.413.39.0.274.274.755.644.0.0.124"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_5"
	         name="{=ObBvcDhJ}fen Giall"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_16"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_5_text}The fen Giall, unsurprisingly for those clans of the Battanian nobility, claim descent from a centuries-long line of ancestors, having ruled the lands of the upper Trand River valley since the times of spirits. A proud people, they once boasted strong relations with the Calradian Empire, whose merchants often frequented the estates of the fen Giall in exchange for their warriors refraining from raiding the imperial borderlands. Whilst this amicable arrangement brought substantial wealth, it also brought the ire of the other Battanian clans, who resented the fen Giall for breaking bread with those they viewed as their oppressors. However, war is now on the doorstep of the fen Giall’s estates, with both the Vlandians and Massa posing a threat to the lands of the western Uchalion Plateau."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.535.39.0.189.178.822.905.0.1.0.535.39.0.178.178.700.904.0.0.0.151.39.0.425.425.773.717.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_4"
	         name="{=k3djFmuO}fen Penraic"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_14"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_4_text}The fen Penraic are one of the younger noble clans of the Battanians, having risen to prominence only a handful of generations ago. Fierce raiders and stalwart warriors, they made their name and fortune in the numerous skirmishes between the Battanians, Vakken and Sturgians, plundering the hillforts of the northerners and coming back with several warlord heads as trophies. Widely feared by the other Battanian noble clans, the fen Penraic jealously eye the position of high king, and there are few who would question, let alone stand in the way of, their single-minded willingness to gain dominance over the Battanian Kingdom."
	         banner_key="11.2.2.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.157.13.13.147.147.764.694.0.0.0.157.13.13.147.147.764.694.0.1.0.527.13.13.111.117.764.951.0.0.90.132.13.13.465.465.764.828.0.0.0.448.13.13.142.126.764.608.0.0.-1.510.13.13.163.83.764.665.0.0.0.503.13.13.55.49.624.753.0.0.6.503.13.13.55.49.904.753.0.0.6"/>
	<Faction id="AR_clan_battania_9"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_battania_9_name}fen Sithigh"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_5_2"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_9_text}The fen Sithigh, like many clans of the Battanian nobility, have a tumultuous story of both growth and decline that can be traced back centuries. The scions of successful merchants who first forged trading connections with the then-nascent Calradian Empire, the fen Sithigh were quick to capitalize on their new mercantile gains, establishing a series of highly profitable emporia across the Uchalion Plateau to trade in the region’s wine, furs and iron ore. However, as with all stories, a rise must inevitably lead to a fall, and the fen Sithigh soon fell afoul of larger and more powerful imperial trade corporations. With their wealth in steady decline, it remains to be seen how long the fen Sithigh can retain their position at the pinnacle of Battanian society."
	         banner_key="11.2.2.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.405.13.13.501.501.764.764.0.0.0.506.13.13.77.113.687.895.0.0.-124.504.13.13.116.152.712.851.0.0.-31.506.13.13.77.113.610.764.0.0.-181.504.13.13.116.152.661.764.0.0.-91.506.13.13.77.113.689.628.0.0.-243.504.13.13.116.152.713.672.0.0.-152.506.13.13.77.113.842.631.0.0.-303.504.13.13.116.152.816.674.0.0.-213.506.13.13.77.113.926.766.0.0.-1.504.13.13.116.152.875.766.0.0.-271.506.13.13.77.113.843.897.0.0.-61.504.13.13.116.152.818.853.0.0.-331"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_8"
	         name="{=14GLGKNj}fen Caernacht"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_B8_l"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_8_text}The fen Caernacht were once one of the most powerful clans of the Battanian nobility, having even held the position of high king for a few generations. However, their primacy in Battanian politics drew envious eyes, and they would soon be unseated by the treachery of the fen Derngil, who it is rumored had the last fen Caernacht high king assassinated and then rigged the noble council election to ensure their own rise to power. Despite little evidence to confirm this story, the fen Caernacht retain a bitter grudge against the fen Derngil, who they view as usurpers. They will follow the will of the high king, albeit with little enthusiasm, if only for the good of the Battanian people as a whole."
	         banner_key="11.2.2.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.415.28.28.481.481.769.764.0.0.0.511.28.28.80.94.767.998.0.1.180.511.28.28.80.94.770.531.0.0.0.511.28.28.80.94.536.762.0.0.89.511.28.28.80.94.1001.765.0.1.270.511.28.28.64.78.920.848.0.1.180.511.28.28.64.78.927.690.0.0.-1.511.28.28.64.78.618.680.0.0.-1.511.28.28.64.78.612.839.0.1.180"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_7"
	         name="{=HMnHaJac}fen Morcar"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_15"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_7_text}The fen Morcar are one of the lesser Battanian noble clans. Whilst many of their peers can claim long lineages of mighty warriors or cunning politicians, the fen Morcar instead claim descent from humble farmers, albeit successful ones. Whilst many in the Battanian borderlands along the Uchalion Massif have historically preferred to raid the soft underbelly of the Calradian Empire, the fen Morcar chose to claim vast tracts of arable land and turn them over to pig farming, becoming the primary source of meat for all Battanians. This has gained them immense wealth, though they are still sneered at by the other Battanian clans for their rustic origins."
	         banner_key="11.2.2.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.407.13.0.509.509.764.757.0.0.-1.413.13.0.62.55.654.869.0.0.315.413.13.0.62.55.879.866.0.1.44.413.13.0.62.55.654.644.0.1.-136.413.13.0.62.55.879.648.0.0.135"/>
	<Faction id="clan_battania_6"
	         name="{=qoLWSdRE}fen Eingal"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_17"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.battania"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_battania_6_text}The fen Eingal clan are one of the most secluded members of the Battanian nobility, having close ties to the Druids of the Ailta Druin. Since time immemorial, they have been the custodians of the ancient customs of wood and spring, and have overseen every major religious event on the Uchalion Plateau since records have been kept. Whilst this role has afforded them little in terms of wealth or material goods, it has afforded them one of the highest stations in the land. Few would dare to question a fen Eingal noble with the druids at his back, and even high kings have been known to quail at their approach."
	         banner_key="11.2.2.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.511.13.0.101.101.773.942.0.0.180.505.13.0.117.117.770.768.0.0.45.511.13.0.101.101.771.595.0.0.0.406.13.0.509.509.769.767.0.0.0.511.13.0.101.101.599.765.0.1.89.511.13.0.101.101.942.770.0.0.270"/>
	<!--
	Calradian Empire
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_1"
	         name="{=OVQoC9fn}Comnos"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_1_8"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_1_text}The Comnos family is a relative newcomer to Calradian politics, claiming their ancestry from humble merchants of the Temea Valley who rose to prominence just over two centuries ago. During the campaigns of the general Sarapios in the north of Calradia, the merchants of the Comnos family gained notoriety for monopolizing the trade of amber and furs with Nordic traders, opening fantastically wealthy emporiums that survive to this day. Known for their cunning and determination in climbing the ladder of Calradian society and politics, demonstrating keen sense for playing both the populists and conservatives within the Senate, they have held the imperial throne for four of generations, and will do anything to maintain their reign."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.323.5.0.442.442.758.728.0.0.0.202.5.0.389.353.834.926.0.0.41.202.5.0.397.397.684.924.0.1.319.523.5.0.162.162.760.754.0.1.0.108.5.0.167.167.760.636.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_1"
	         name="{=hrWQWgaM}Pethros"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_47"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_1_text}The Pethros are one of Calradia’s oldest families, claiming their descent from one of the companions of Calradios the Great. They have ruled the rich lands around Lycaron for centuries, making their fortune in the raising and trading of fine thoroughbred horses, that are renowned throughout Calradia. Whilst they have never held the imperial throne, generations of Pethros noblemen have contented themselves with being the chief advisor to various Calradian emperors, a title passed from father to son over the centuries. Indeed, many upstart emperors have found their reigns made, or unmade, by the simple word of the patriarch of the Pethros family."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.200.5.0.200.200.614.894.0.0.0.200.5.0.200.200.914.894.0.1.0.100.5.0.430.413.764.694.0.1.0.326.5.0.170.164.763.949.0.1.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_2"
	         name="{=UQHUu2bj}Leonipardes"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_48"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_2_text}The Leonipardes were one of the earliest families to cross the Zeos River and found estates east of the Temea valley, gaining renown across the Calradian Empire for leading the charge of eastward colonisation. Their villas, located around the southern tip of the Ilataric Hills, are famed for producing uncommonly fine wines, and have hosted a cast of emperors, generals and senators over the centuries. Whilst not necessarily the wealthiest of Calradia’s noble families, nor the most renowned on the field of battle, few can rival the Leonipardes for their pedigree, and their sons are widely acclaimed from the Senate to the frontiers of the Calradian Empire."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.214.5.0.350.350.768.758.0.0.0.423.5.0.491.491.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_4"
	         name="{=xqkKtWqa}Elaches"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_40"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_4_text}The Elaches hail from the verdant lands along the banks of the Aris River, known widely as the breadbasket of the Calradian Empire. In centuries past, it was their ancestors who cleared the land of its dense forests - and much of its Dryatic population - to create one of the most productive farming landscapes on the continent. Unsurprisingly, this has brought the Elaches a great deal of wealth and prestige in Calradian society, earning them a permanent seat on the Calradian Senate. Viewed by some nobles as little more than upstart farmers, the Elaches are strong believers in the unity of the Calradian Empire, and will do anything necessary to end the civil war as soon as possible."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.201.5.0.350.350.884.779.0.0.180.201.5.0.450.450.764.749.0.0.0.201.5.0.350.350.644.779.0.0.180.500.5.0.600.600.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_7"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_7_name}Sonoros"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_58"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_7_text}The Sonoros family have the claim to being one of Calradia’s oldest families, though not perhaps its most renowned. They are descended from Calradian traders who, in the time before Calradios the Great’s landing at Charasea, established a small emporium on the Biscan Coast, trading with the Palaic and Battanian peoples of the region. After the founding of the Calradian Empire, they moved steadily westward, eventually coming to construct a small estate in the Dryatic Mountains. Whilst they do not count many senators or generals amongst their forebears, they have always been a staunch supporter of imperial authority, following the Dragon Banner wherever it may fly."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.502.5.0.450.450.764.764.0.0.0.103.5.0.300.300.749.764.0.0.0.523.5.0.200.200.764.584.0.0.0.202.5.0.200.200.771.853.0.1.-23"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_6"
	         name="{=BxCRDt5m}Vizartos"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_54"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_6_text}The Vizartos family, unlike many of their peers in the southern regions of the Calradian Empire, cannot claim descent from the great and good of the continent’s past. Instead, the ancestors of the Vizartos were mercenaries of the Palaic Myzean people, who came to settle at the head of the Sethys Valley in the decades immediately preceding the expansion of the Calradians into the region. Initially siding with the local Palaic people against the newcomers, the Vizartos soon had a change of heart, betraying their people for the promises of the Calradian Empire. Known as a slightly drab and serious people, they now rule over one of the most productive lands on the continent."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.435.5.0.508.508.770.792.0.0.0.423.5.0.507.507.763.751.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_4"
	         name="{=4Dbwdjbe}Hongeros"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_30"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_4_text}The Hongeros are another of the Calradian Empire’s oldest aristocratic families, claiming descent from the great-nephew of Calradios the Great. Often derided by younger noble families for their elitism, they live by the motto that 'it is better that one be ruled by the well-fed than the hungry, by one satisfied thief than a hundred frustrated thieves'. From their rich seaside estates along the coast of the Perassic Sea, the Hongeros dominate Calradian politics from afar, and the names of their sons are counted among the rolls of successful senators and generals alike."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.418.5.0.150.150.614.914.0.0.0.107.5.0.550.550.764.739.0.0.0.418.5.0.150.150.914.914.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_8"
	         name="{=8Wi66Sp2}Prienicos"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_72"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_8_text}The Prienicos family originally hail from the island of Perassis Major, in the middle of the Perassic Sea. Assimilated into Calradian society centuries ago, following the capture of the island in the Quyazic Wars, they proved to be enthusiastic leaders in the Calradian Senate, often speaking on matters of imperial importance. Moving from their island home to the southern regions of the Calradian Empire, they now lay claim to a large estate in the fertile area of the Sethys Valley known as Tripotamia. Not particularly free-thinking, they content themselves with simply following the current Calradian Emperor, whoever they may be."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.147.5.0.456.456.766.765.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_3"
	         name="{=h7ujXmDx}Mestricaros"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_17"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_s"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_3_text}The Mestricaros family have the dubious honor of being the most besieged noble house in Calradia, holding their southern borderland home against all comers for the best part of three centuries. In their time, they have seen the coming and going of uncountable Padishahs, Khans and Emirs, with each generation of Mestricaros learning the hardships of warfare. They look upon the many other noble families of Calradia with relative distaste, resenting that they must bear the burden of keeping the lands of others safe. However, there are none in the Calradian Empire who can deny the loyalty of the Mestricaros to the idea of empire, nor any more proud in flying its banners."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.108.5.0.485.485.769.650.0.0.0.325.5.0.501.501.765.818.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Eastern Calradian Despotate
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_3"
	         name="{=txCNVmSV}Neretzes"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_1_5"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_3_text}The Neretzes family is among the oldest and most respected in Calradia, claiming descent from one of the original followers of Calradios the Great. Indeed, one may find a member of the Neretzes in almost every town of the Calradian Empire, attending to matters of state, civil administration, or serving in the legions. However, in recent years, the rebellion of Solarios split the proud and mighty dynasty. Though the majority remain loyal to their patriarch, and so found their way into the eastern rebel empire, some Neretzes may be found in both the courts of Zeonica and Charasea. Whilst perhaps out of favor with many in the Calradian nobility, none can deny that the Neretzes may mobilize wealth and prestige, without equal, to achieve their goals."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.200.5.0.276.240.660.820.0.0.341.200.5.0.276.240.869.822.0.1.18.200.5.0.276.240.660.820.0.0.341.200.5.0.276.240.869.822.0.1.18.419.5.0.223.203.766.722.0.0.-90.522.5.0.77.74.763.955.0.0.359.522.5.0.77.74.763.955.0.0.359.527.5.0.77.69.763.579.0.0.0.527.5.0.77.69.763.579.0.0.0.527.5.0.70.63.763.579.0.0.0.527.5.0.72.65.763.579.0.0.0.503.5.0.29.33.763.986.0.0.359.503.5.0.29.33.733.955.0.0.359.503.5.0.29.33.794.955.0.0.359"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_2"
	         name="{=UW8BjPXR}Argoros"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_3"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_2_text}The Argoros are one of the more recent additions to the aristocracy of the Calradian Empire, being founded by the two brothers Neros and Leonicos, who made their fortunes as advocates in the imperial courts of Zeonica. Renowned as staunch supporters of the Senate, law and order, their path in recent years has taken an interesting turn. Like many houses, the crisis facing the Calradian Empire has torn the Argoros family apart, with many deciding to serve the rebel Emperor Solarios in his eastern separatist regime, fighting against the very laws they once claimed to uphold."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.500.5.0.550.550.764.769.0.0.0.142.5.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.0.423.5.0.560.520.764.769.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_1"
	         name="{=fXENjJJL}Osticos"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_1"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_1_text}The Osticos family claims descent from the sworn bodyguard of Calradios the Great. This clout has rewarded them handsomely, with a vast network of clients - and their money, serving the interests of the Osticos over countless generations. Despite this, the Osticos can only claim one Calradian Emperor in their lineage, resulting in great resentment every time an imperial claimant is chosen from another family. This has given them a reputation for a strong sense of entitlement, and there are few in the senate who respect their grandiose claims to power and prestige. Increasingly marginalized, they decided to support the rebel Emperor Solarios, hoping his conquests may improve their prospects at ultimate power."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.338.5.0.490.490.764.764.0.0.0.104.5.0.204.204.630.887.0.0.0.341.5.0.204.204.898.888.0.1.0.523.5.0.122.122.761.620.0.1.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_5"
	         name="{=6OEQJV6k}Julios"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_63"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_5_text}The Julios family holds one of the proudest military traditions in the Calradian Empire, serving in the vaunted legions from the earliest Calradian wars of expansion to the present. For generations, they have been based primarily in the camps of the eastern legions, fighting incursions from steppe nomads and the Darshi Empire alike. They naturally sided with Solarios in his eastern wars, then willingly followed him into secession from the empire. Derided for their disloyalty, many in the Calradian nobility believe the Julios will simply follow whoever offers them a chance at winning glory in battle."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.217.5.0.351.351.769.855.0.0.0.119.5.0.398.398.766.706.0.0.0.512.5.0.156.156.959.862.0.0.0.512.5.0.156.156.595.871.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_5"
	         name="{=4rr3d8hY}Dolentos"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_50"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_5_text}The Dolentos are another of noble families of the Calradian Empire drawn to the service in the legions. Founded just four generations ago by the 'Master of Horse' to the first Emperor of the Comnos Dynasty, they have gained acclaim as formidable leaders of the Calradian Empire’s auxiliary forces, carving a bloody wake through all in their path. Their ruthless efficiency has seen them go far in Calradian politics, being promoted to manage the prominent eastern town of Myzea. Offered a chance to lead legions by Solarios, the Dolentos family gladly joined his rebellion, winning the dubious acclaim of being one of the most competent leaders in the unfolding Calradian civil war."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.8690.8690.590.796.1.0.0.331.5.0.400.400.765.716.0.0.0.202.5.0.400.400.862.877.0.0.55.202.5.0.402.423.663.874.0.1.303"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_6"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_6_name}Lascaris"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_51"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_6_text}The Lascaris are an ignoble representative of the nobility of the Calradian Empire, claiming their descent from a former quartermaster in the Calradian Empire's eastern legions. It is widely believed that they bought their way into the aristocracy with a fortune made by re-selling old equipment from the legions back to the state. Sneered at by the other families as being frauds, the Lascaris naturally saw the potential profits to be had in Solarios' rebellion, as well as their chance at revenge on the other families. Whilst their reputation has gained them few friends among the other noble families, their cunning has seen the troops of the Lascaris become some of the best-equipped fighters in the land, making them a formidable adversary."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.2000.2000.764.764.1.0.0.500.5.0.500.500.764.764.0.1.180.405.5.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.0.423.5.0.600.550.764.764.0.0.180.521.5.0.100.100.764.514.0.0.180"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_7"
	         name="{=Ds2vQVwr}Avlonos"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_55"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_7_text}The Avlonos family is a lesson in the perils of a mercantile life in the Calradian Empire. Descended from a long line of settler-farmers who colonized the Myzead in the years following the Calradian conquest of the region, the Avlonos originally joined their peers in raising cattle among the rocky, windswept crags of their new home. However, generations ago an enterprizing member of the Avlonos saw the potential profit to be made in the trade of silk from the east into the Calradian Empire, trading the simple pastures of the land for a stand of mulberry trees. Whilst initially successful in producing some of the only silk from within Calradia itself, the Avlonos were soon undercut by the ever-zealous merchants of the east. Now beggared, the Avlonos have taken to a soldier’s life, willingly following Solarios in his rebellion."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.459.5.0.300.300.764.750.0.0.0.423.5.0.500.500.764.752.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_south_9"
	         name="{=xbkYPXCt}Vetranis"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_SE9_l"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_south_9_text}The Vetranis family, as their name may suggest, originate from veterans of the Calradian Empire’s eastern legions. In centuries past, they followed the Dragon Banner of Calradios in campaigns from the frigid forests of the north, to the desolate sands of the Nahasa, and now to the fractious eastern borderlands. Rewarded for their generations of service to the Calradian Empire with a minor lordship of one of the borderland fortresses, the Vetranis have since repelled many incursions of peoples from the Calradian steppe, seeing off khans and shahs alike. A staunch supporter of Solarios in his eastern campaigns, they naturally supported the rebel general in his bid for the Calradian throne."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.505.5.0.460.50.764.764.0.0.0.459.5.0.150.150.659.658.0.0.0.459.5.0.150.150.870.658.0.0.0.459.5.0.150.150.870.870.0.0.0.459.5.0.150.150.659.870.0.0.0.505.5.0.460.50.764.764.0.0.90"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_8"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_8_name}Diogenos"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_NE8_l"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_8_text}The Diogenos family is one of the great success stories of Calradicization. Originally cattle farmers of the Palaic Myzean people, the decades after the Calradian conquest of the Myzead saw a great social metamorphosis for the Avlonos. Realizing the inescapable fact that the legions of the Calradian Empire consumed a prodigious amount of food, the scions of the Avlonos came to monopolize the supply of beef to the legions, accumulating in just two short generations a fortune to rival many of the oldest families of the Calradian nobility. Sneered at by such families as nothing more than upstart rustics, the Avlonos naturally came to side with Solarios in his rebellion and now lead the very legions they once served."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.335.5.0.350.350.764.764.0.1.0.500.5.0.500.510.764.764.0.0.0.500.5.0.450.450.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Western Calradian Republic
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_9"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_9_name}Heraclinos"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.lord_NE9_l"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_9_text}The Heraclinos family have called the city of Charasea home since the days of Calradios the Great. One of the first families to settle in the city after its foundation, they were soon to establish themselves as one of the most wealthy and influential families in the Calradian Kingdom, monopolizing the trade of exotic goods from the Kannic colonies of Quyaz into the nascent kingdom. Chosen by Calradios to govern the city of Charasea - a title that generations of Heraclinos have held for the centuries since, they now find themselves at a crossroads. With the rise of the Vlandian Kingdom bringing warfare to their doorstep, the Heraclinos now defend their ancestral home against all comers, rallying the dispossessed families of the western provinces of the Calradian Empire to their banner."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.8690.8690.590.796.1.0.0.401.5.0.335.335.769.775.0.0.15.401.5.0.170.170.769.775.0.0.29.503.5.0.59.57.769.775.0.0.15.423.5.0.500.511.767.784.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_3"
	         name="{=tdGvElSy}Dionicos"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_11"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_3_text}The Dionicos family are deeply rooted to the west of Calradia, raising horses and cultivating grain in the rich lands around Paravenos for centuries. Indeed, for many in the Calradian Empire, the title of 'Governor of the Western Capital' was almost synonymous with the name Dionicos. However, with the coming of the Vlandians and their kin, they now find themselves as refugees - their former lands forever lost to them. They are the greatest champion of the cause to reconquer the western provinces, and will fight to the bitter end to reclaim what they have lost."
	         banner_key="11.8.8.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.300.39.39.221.238.648.848.0.1.90.202.39.39.347.465.738.720.0.1.-65.510.39.39.117.88.766.876.0.1.-181.300.39.39.221.238.889.848.0.0.269.336.39.39.165.162.774.666.0.1.0.202.39.39.347.465.798.716.0.0.62.510.39.39.136.88.766.894.0.1.-181.510.39.39.166.88.766.912.0.1.-181.510.39.39.250.88.766.930.0.1.-181"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_2"
	         name="{=a4GxTbPD}Varros"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_9"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_2_text}The Varros, like many families of the western provinces of the Calradian Empire, lay claim to a long lineage of proud and powerful figures in Calradia’s history. However, there are few who claim the Varros deserve to be called ‘noble’. Their estates around the city of Ortysia are known as the most miserable places in the Calradian Empire - places of extortionate taxes, dour villagers and overworked slaves. This has made the Varros one of the most wealthy families on the continent, though also one of the most despised. With few friends among the Calradian nobility, they seized the opportunities provided by secession, and so joined with the other families of the western provinces in rebellion."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.337.5.0.454.454.759.690.0.0.0.301.5.0.322.322.756.916.0.0.90.301.5.0.322.322.765.981.0.0.270"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_5"
	         name="{=cd0yDTM1}Lonalion"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_45"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_5_text}The Lonalion are renowned as the leaders of the Calradian populist movement, agitating for better land and employment rights for the poor of the vast urban cities of the Calradian Empire. However, such rights have remained largely static over the centuries, and the poor continue to live in squalor, whilst the Lonalion have gained great power and prestige in the Calradian Senate. This has led many to believe that their words are, in fact, hollow - a mask for their true political ambitions. Distrustful of the growing authority of the Comnos Dynasty and seeing in equal parts the threat and opportunity posed by the Vlandians and their kin, they have rallied their numerous supporters in service of the secessionists of Charasea."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.523.5.0.299.299.762.774.0.0.0.500.5.0.508.510.764.771.0.0.0.500.5.0.442.442.764.771.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_north_4"
	         name="{=tA3IRBgv}Impestores"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_20"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_north_4_text}The Impestores are the nobility of the Neurval - the valley just north of the ancestral home of the Calradian Empire on the Bay of Charasea. One of the first regions to be colonized by the nascent Calradian Kingdom, during the later years of the reign of Calradios the Great, the Impestores have held the rulership of the region since that time. This has made them one of the oldest and most storied families of the Calradian nobility, even boasting Echerion the Tyrant-Slayer, founder of the Calradian Republic, as one of their ancestors. However, the last century has seen the Impestores’ homeland threatened, first by Battanian raiders, and now by the very Vlandians who were charged with their defense, and so they must fight for survival."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.304.5.0.450.450.914.764.0.0.0.443.5.0.550.550.774.764.0.0.0.304.5.0.450.450.614.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_6"
	         name="{=ApJrV7bA}Sorados"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_52"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_6_text}The Sorados family is a relative newcomer to the Calradian aristocracy, being founded just over a century ago by successful miners. Seeing the potential riches to be had on the northern slopes of Mount Aracathos, the Sorados were the first to sink an exploratory shaft into the mountainside, hitting a seam of rich silver ore almost immediately. Within just a generation, their mines would expand to span nearly the entirety of the mountain range, with vast lodes of silver and iron bringing great wealth and status. With threats looming over their southern and western neighbors, the Sorados sided with the secessionist senators in Charasea, turning their wealth to the matter of war."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.336.5.0.486.486.761.813.0.0.0.340.5.0.279.279.764.522.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_7"
	         name="{=bjemmmcF}Corenios"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_53"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_7_text}The Corenios, unlike many of their counterparts in the aristocracy of the western provinces of the Calradian Empire, are a marcher family charged with protecting the Calradian border with the Uchalion Massif - the craggy highland territory of the Battanians. Over the centuries, they have shed blood and suffered much in the defense of their homeland, keeping the wealthy interior lands of the Calradian Empire safe from invaders. Though often overlooked in upholding their little-recognized and thankless task, the Corenios are nonetheless stalwart supporters of the senators in Charasea, protecting the western lands against all comers, both old and new."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.423.5.0.486.486.765.760.0.0.0.340.5.0.316.316.764.739.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_8"
	         name="{=pdz4YsEf}Maneolis"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_1_71"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_8_text}The Maneolis once held lands on the Biscan coast, making their fame and fortune from growing fine grapes for the production of a wine renowned across the continent. However, their recent history is one of strife and decline, first suffering near-constant raids from the Nords, and now finding themselves dispossessed of their estates by the nascent Vlandian Kingdom. Arriving at the court of the secessionist senate at Charasea, without land and nearly destitute, they willingly joined the many other families of the western provinces in attempting to reclaim their homeland, being given a chance to found fresh estates in the fertile lands along the Zeos River."
	         banner_key="11.71.4.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.419.5.0.503.503.770.775.0.0.0.335.5.0.143.143.878.652.0.0.325.335.5.0.143.143.654.657.0.0.42.335.5.0.143.143.652.886.0.0.134.335.5.0.143.143.880.892.0.0.214"/>
	<Faction id="clan_empire_west_9"
	         name="{=LTWTTQ71}Palladios"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_WE9_l"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.empire_w"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_empire_west_9_text}The Palladios family have a lowly reputation, being known by the other families of the western provinces of the Calradian Empire as reclusive hermits, dwelling in the isolated far reaches of the Bay of Ortysia, beyond the eastern reaches of the Temea Mountains. They live a simple lifestyle, growing grapes in rich volcanic soils and surviving off the bountiful seafood pulled from the Perassic Sea. However, when called, there are fewer more renowned warriors in the Calradian Empire, with the legions of the Palladios found following the Dragon Banner in almost every major battle in Calradia’s history. With the threat posed by the Vlandians, the Palladios naturally found themselves aligned with the secessionist senate in Charasea."
	         banner_key="11.8.8.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.457.9.9.131.150.648.786.0.0.90.533.9.9.148.155.766.784.0.0.90.457.9.9.131.150.883.786.0.1.-90.457.9.9.136.154.883.786.0.1.-90.457.9.9.137.156.648.786.0.0.90.533.9.9.149.157.766.784.0.0.90.106.9.9.391.346.766.612.0.0.359.510.9.9.50.79.765.1026.0.1.269.528.9.9.91.56.765.809.0.1.-1.500.9.9.67.68.766.866.0.1.-1.500.9.9.64.65.766.866.0.1.-1.500.9.9.59.60.766.866.0.1.-1.500.9.9.55.56.766.866.0.1.-1.503.9.9.29.29.766.866.0.1.-1.500.9.9.59.60.766.924.0.1.-1.500.9.9.57.57.766.924.0.1.-1.500.9.9.53.53.766.924.0.1.-1.500.9.9.50.50.766.924.0.1.-1.503.9.9.29.29.766.924.0.1.-1.500.9.9.53.54.767.976.0.1.-1.500.9.9.51.51.767.976.0.1.-1.500.9.9.48.48.767.976.0.1.-1.500.9.9.45.45.767.976.0.1.-1.503.9.9.26.26.767.976.0.1.-1.510.9.9.32.52.765.1047.0.1.179.506.9.9.38.46.765.1053.0.1.269.521.9.9.35.35.766.787.0.1.-1.528.9.9.91.56.765.765.0.0.180.457.9.9.131.150.883.786.0.1.-90"/>
	<!--
	Iltanlar Khanate
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_1_name}Turakizt"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_6_1"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_1_text}The Turakizt are the current ruling family of the Iltanlar, claiming divine descent from one of the ten sons of the mythical she-wolf. Centuries ago, their ancestors descended from the highlands beyond the Sulun Dag Mountains, displacing the local nomadic tribes and founding the fortress city of Baltakhand. Since that time, other nomadic tribes have flocked to their banners, settling far and wide across the Devseg to form one of the largest realms in Calradia. The Turakizt hold together their fragile alliance of tribes with an iron fist, quashing the more independent-minded beys and maintaining a tight grip on the movements of traders across their lands from the Darshi and Calradian empires, thus securing the wealth and prestige of their people."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.449.11.0.309.319.764.654.0.0.0.449.11.0.309.319.764.884.0.0.180.510.11.0.351.240.643.769.0.0.180.510.11.0.351.240.886.769.0.0.180.500.11.0.500.500.764.771.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_2_name}Gunalait"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_3"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_2_text}The Gunalait, like many of their kin, descend from nomads of Calradia’s eastern steppe who migrated into the region known as the Devseg many centuries ago. Similar to their Turakizt overlords, they have monopolized the movement of silks and spices through their lands, growing immensely wealthy as middlemen in the trade routes of both the Darshi and Calradian empires. However, it is in the art of war that the Gunalait are most renowned. Born for the saddle and bow, the battle cries of their riders bringing terror to any who would dare stand in their way."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.449.11.0.309.319.764.654.0.0.0.449.11.0.309.319.764.884.0.0.180.510.11.0.351.240.643.769.0.0.180.510.11.0.351.240.886.769.0.0.180.500.11.0.500.500.764.771.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_3_name}Baljugit"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_5"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_3_text}The Baljugit tribe are one of the most ancient among the Iltanlar, having dwelt in the foothills south of the Sulun Dag Mountains for almost a millennium. Unlike many of their kin, the Baljugit are not a migratory people, preferring instead to live in clusters of yurts on the fringes of the only woodland found on the Devseg Plateau, felling trees and raising herds of horses and goats in the small forest clearings. This life has made them a hardy people, as well-adjusted to survival in the woods as life in the saddle , and their axemen are renowned across the lands of the Calradian steppe."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.127.11.0.165.165.769.574.0.0.0.307.11.0.508.508.764.754.0.0.45.503.11.0.165.165.764.904.0.0.0.307.11.0.508.508.764.754.0.1.-45"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_4_name}Kurtogulit"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_16"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_4_text}The Kurtogulit tribe are an outlier in Iltanlar society, preferring to traverse the world by boat and oar than in the saddle. Originating from settlements along the highland tributaries of the Karakaz River, they have grown wealthy off centuries of controlling the riverine trade between the Byalic peoples of the northeast, and the Palaics and then Calradians of the southwest. Much like the Byals, the Kurtogulit have in more recent times become victims of the westward expansion of the Nachaghan tribe, being forced to migrate from their ancestral homeland downriver to the Iltan Portages. Gaining a hard lesson in warfare, they now serve as border guards of the Khanate, protecting the Iltan Portages from both east and west."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.436.11.0.438.438.769.769.0.0.0.503.11.0.100.100.585.767.0.0.0.503.11.0.100.100.943.767.0.0.0.521.11.0.100.100.765.556.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_5"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_5_name}Ayangait"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_17"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_5_text}The Ayangait, like many among the Iltanlar, migrated into the lands west of the Sulun Dag Mountains centuries ago, mobilizing their numerous slaves to build the fortress known today as Kaysar Castle. From this place, they have served as the guard of the northern approaches to Baltakhand, growing wealthy in the process through taxing travellers and merchants heading to the capital of the Iltanlar Khanate. They are renowned as fierce warriors, skilled in both the bow and lance, ranging from their fortress seat to drove vast herds of horses from the Karakaz River to Tsanga Nor, terrorizing villagers along the Darshi and Calradian borders as they go."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.428.11.0.438.438.764.784.0.0.0.503.11.0.211.211.764.809.0.0.358.214.11.0.243.243.764.641.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_6"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_6_name}Himaxar"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_18_1"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_6_text}The Himaxar are one of the lesser-known tribes of the Iltanlar. Sons and daughters of a long line of warriors, they have loyally served the ruling Turakizt tribe for the past two centuries, fighting in their many wars against the neighboring tribes of the Calradian steppe. Whilst this has gained them much in the way of wealth through the spoils of battle, the hordes sing little of their heroics on the field, nor of their nobility in court. Instead, those who know the Himaxar have a rather bleak view, calling them nothing more than bandits and cutthroats, loyal to their friends, but deadly to their foes."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.500.11.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.150.11.0.400.400.768.784.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_7"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_7_name}Aizrit"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_19"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_7_text}The Aizrit claim descent from a long lineage of mystics and shamans. Like many among the Iltanlar, they believe that their ancestor was one of the ten sons of the mythical she-wolf, who mounted the horse of night and now rides across the sky with a great wolf pack. Whilst many in Calradia view this as little more than petty superstition, the Aizrit live and die by this belief, and carry it across the steppe with them, preaching to any who will listen. In battle, they are formidable adversaries, known for sacrificing captured enemies in brutal blood rituals."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.780.802.1.0.0.117.11.0.250.250.782.758.0.0.0.502.11.0.350.350.764.764.0.0.45.521.11.0.100.100.821.839.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_8"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_8_name}Mazalar"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_6_20"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_8_text}The Mazalar, unlike most prominent tribes of the Iltanlar, have only recently moved into the lands of the Devseg, riding down from the highland foothills of the Sulun Dag Mountains to seize a foothold around the fortress known as Tepes Castle. A violent and cruel people, even their Iltanlar kin regard them as savage and ignoble, and their subjects and slaves are among the most miserable in Calradia. However, their use to the khans of Baltakhand is readily apparent, and so the Mazalar now form the vanguard of the nomadic hosts, riding along the borderlands with the Darshi city states and fighting any who dare to cross them."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.126.11.0.250.250.764.764.0.0.0.510.11.0.250.200.914.644.0.0.90.510.11.0.250.200.914.884.0.0.90.510.11.0.250.200.614.884.0.0.90.510.11.0.250.200.614.644.0.0.90.521.11.0.150.150.764.554.0.0.0.503.11.0.150.150.764.974.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_khuzait_9"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_9_name}Ixgchit"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_K9_l"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.khuzait"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_khuzait_9_text}The Ixgchit have the dubious honor of calling the lands of the southern Devseg their home, raising vast herds of horses in the sparse, windblown grasslands in the foothills of the Kohi Ajik - the so-called ‘Lover’s Mountain’. Whilst these lands have brought great wealth to the Ixgchit, their proximity to the borderlands of the Darshi Empire has frequently brought them into conflict with the forces of the Padishah. This has hardened the Ixgchit into formidable warriors, serving as the bulwark of the Iltanlar realm against their numerous southern foes."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.510.11.0.351.240.764.894.0.0.0.510.11.0.351.240.764.649.0.0.0.500.11.0.500.500.764.771.0.0.0.145.11.0.351.240.769.774.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Sturgian Confederation
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_1"
	         name="{=A4wIVnM4}Gundaroving"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_1"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_1_text}The Gundaroving, despite being the most powerful of the Sturgian ruling families, are not in fact Sturgians. They claim descent from the Nord warrior and explorer Gundar, who in a battle near the town of Balgard managed to outwit a combined force of Sturgians and Vakken, defeating them in a battle of words and thus claiming rulership over them. Unlike many among their Nordic kin, the Gundaroving are not a particularly restless or warlike people, instead preferring to settle disputes by cunning diplomacy. However, if pushed far enough, few survive the wrath of the Gundaroving, whose huscarls have beheaded many a lord or king who was foolish enough to test the limits of their patience. Though they are not absolute rulers, there are many who fear that the scions of Gundar seek to make themselves a monarch over all Sturgians, and so their position remains a tenuous one at best."
	         banner_key="11.71.12.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.333.111.0.487.487.756.750.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_5"
	         name="{=s0AVQCbJ}Togaroving"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_17"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_5_text}The Togaroving are the ruling family of the ancient Sturgian city of Revyl, having dwelled in the Kachyar Peninsula since time immemorial. They are a stoic people, driven by a desire to maintain the power and prestige of their family, as well as the prominence of Revyl in Sturgian society. This position has made them a number of enemies, though most notably the Togaroving have found a powerful rival and foe in the Gundaroving, who they view as little more than Nordic raiders and usurpers. Despite their animosity, they remain cunning politicians, hiding their distain behind wise words and wry expressions."
	         banner_key="11.71.12.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.456.111.0.504.504.770.698.0.0.359.444.111.0.116.116.764.923.0.0.179.454.111.0.116.116.889.922.0.0.179.454.111.0.116.116.649.921.0.0.359"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_3_name}Hayekoving"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_5"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_3_text}The Hayekoving, unlike many of their Sturgian kin, are not a family renowned for their prowess in battle. Instead, they prefer the subtler arts of trading, running a series of emporiums across the northern lands buying furs and amber from the local Vakken population and selling them on to the citizens of the Calradian Empire. Such an enterprise has brought them much acclaim from the Vakken people who inhabit the lands around their estate of Sibir, however little in the way of riches. Indeed, though few know of it, the Hayekoving are almost entirely broke, trading more on their reputation and political favors now, rather than gold or silver."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.432.39.0.450.450.764.764.0.0.0.415.39.0.150.150.634.944.0.0.0.415.39.0.150.150.894.944.0.0.0.415.39.0.150.150.894.584.0.0.0.415.39.0.150.150.634.584.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_8"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_8_name}Nowyraving"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_20"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_8_text}The Nowyraving family claim an ancient lineage, descending from Sturgian adventurers and settlers who founded the colony of Varcheg in centuries long past. However, whereas many among the Sturgian nobility have seen relatively constant growth in their wealth and power, the Nowyraving have instead seen constant hardship. Whilst the location of their estates at Varcheg have afforded them an enviable position at the nexus of Calradia’s northern fur trade - a position that has undoubtedly brought wealth and status – this very position has also drawn the attention of other Strugian nobles, eager to usurp the Nowyraving and claim the trade as their own. Whilst the Nowyraving have admirably defended their claim, the recent interest of the Gundaroving in Varcheg and its trade have some questioning how long the Nowyraving may endure in this hostile new world."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.138.39.0.350.450.864.764.0.0.0.138.39.0.350.450.664.764.0.1.0.521.39.0.150.150.764.839.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_2"
	         name="{=Eu932blQ}Kuloving"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_3"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_2_text}The Kuloving are one of the most ancient families among the Sturgian nobility, claiming to have held mastery of the sacred woods north of the town of Omor since the dawn of time. It is they who keep the hidden paths between the trees and rivers, who know where to find the springs in which gods and spirits dwell. This reputation of godly knowledge has brought the Kuloving great respect from the other nobles of the Sturgians and Vakken, who frequently attend their woodland estates for matters of ritual or ceremony. Indeed, it is said that none may call themselves a true ruler of the Sturgians without the consent of the Kuloving and, of course, the gods they serve."
	         banner_key="11.12.12.4345.4345.776.778.1.0.0.533.140.140.252.254.710.889.0.0.88.533.140.140.252.254.818.889.0.0.88.503.140.140.43.45.707.897.0.0.-1.503.140.140.43.45.821.895.0.0.-1.515.140.140.43.45.927.895.0.0.-1.515.140.140.43.45.604.895.0.0.-1.415.140.140.105.106.873.943.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.873.943.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.873.943.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.764.949.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.764.949.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.764.949.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.656.949.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.656.949.0.0.179.415.140.140.105.106.656.949.0.0.179.332.140.140.388.314.759.709.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_7"
	         name="{=xw0eTkkb}Vezhoving"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_19"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_7_text}The Vezhoving, much like their Gundaroving patrons, are a family of Nordic warriors who have come to rule over the lands of the Sturgians. Whereas the Gundaroving sailed east into the Byalic Sea, the Vezhoving sailed west, coming to settle in a small, fortified camp on the coast of the Bay of Varcheg that they named Nevyansk. Over the generations, Sturgian settlers congregated around the Vezhoving’s estate, forming a small yet powerful chiefdom. However, the proximity of the Vezhoving to the lands of the Battanians has brought great risk, and so they spend most of their time fighting off raids from their neighbors, rather than engaging in broader Sturgian politics."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.439.39.0.400.300.764.844.0.1.180.438.39.0.400.400.764.634.0.1.180"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_9"
	         name="{=WssI6mOE}Kostoroving"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_S9_l"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_9_text}The Kostoroving family have the dubious honor of controlling the western borderlands of the Sturgian territories, their estates standing proudly on the eastern bank of the Vastra River in opposition to the Battanian and Vakken lands beyond. Whilst Sturgian by ancestry, generations of intermarriage with Nord warriors and maidens have brought many of the sturdy northerners to the Kostoroving banner, growing their modest holdings into one of the more powerful of the Sturgian chiefdoms. Indeed, there are few in the northern lands of Calradia who would willingly cross swords or axes with the Kostoroving, their reputation earning them a place of high regard among the north men."
	         banner_key="11.71.12.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.142.29.149.397.397.767.621.0.0.0.146.29.149.374.374.767.870.0.1.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_4"
	         name="{=AppNvfPv}Ormidoving"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_16"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_4_text}The Ormidoving - the ‘House of Orm’ - claim descent from a long line of Nordic warriors and raiders, who settled in the lands along the southern coast of the Byalic Sea in centuries past. Whilst many Nord families managed to integrate into Sturgian society relatively peacefully, the Ormidoving have instead earned a fearsome reputation as some of the most bloodthirsty warriors in the northern lands, having settled many a feud with their rival Sturgian clans at the edge of an axe blade. The position of their estates in the isolated north has proved most fruitful. The multitude of local Vakken tribes fell easily to the Ormidoving warriors, and now provide them with vast quantities of tribute, making them one of the wealthiest of the Sturgian chiefdoms."
	         banner_key="11.71.12.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.307.111.0.416.416.781.835.0.0.180.307.111.0.416.416.793.720.0.0.0.442.111.0.310.310.673.844.0.0.180.442.111.0.310.310.901.718.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_sturgia_6"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_6_name}Svehlaving"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_18"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.sturgia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_sturgia_6_text}The Svehlaving are a proud and ancient Sturgian family, tracing their ancestry back to the days before the arrival of Calradios the Great on the continent. Whilst many such prestigious families have fallen victim to centuries of Nordic incursions and usurpations, the Svehlaving have managed to preserve the integrity of their chiefdom and estates, albeit at the cost of much of their fortune. Instead of attempting to resist the Nords, the Svehlaving prefer to hire them, attracting quite the cadre of huscarls to their banner. This makes them a force to be reckoned with, and there are few in the northern lands of Calradia who would dare to cross them."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.444.39.0.400.500.764.764.0.0.0.434.39.0.400.500.664.764.0.0.0.434.39.0.400.500.864.764.0.1.0"/>
	<!--
	Vlandian Kingdom
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_1"
	         name="{=3o5s6L3y}dey Meroc"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_4_1"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_1_text}The dey Meroc are one of the oldest houses of the Vlandian nobility, having dwelt along the Biscan coast since the days of Wilund the Bold. For generations, they eked out an existence selling salted fish to the Calradian citizens of the city of Ialonos - located near to their village. However, their fortunes would change when they enlisted in the service of the Calradian Emperor Phamynor, winning wealth and renown for themselves campaigning against the Darshi in the distant east of the continent. An independent-minded people, the dey Meroc have long held ambitions for an independent Vlandian kingdom, preferably with them at its head. Seizing the opportunity afforded to them by the interregnum in the Calradian Empire, they have achieved just that, and now they stand at the head of a vast kingdom, fighting for independence against the very Calradian authorities they once served."
	         banner_key="11.71.14.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.346.15.0.509.509.770.757.0.0.0.424.15.0.213.213.585.771.0.0.0.424.15.0.213.213.951.763.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_7"
	         name="{=LZVzzczs}dey Fortes"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_23"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_7_text}The dey Fortes, like many of the noble houses of the Vlandians, cannot claim descent from the wealthy or influential of Calradia’s past. Their ancestors were humble travellers who sailed across the Western Ocean in search of a better life, settling on the Ebor Peninsula in the growing Vlandian enclave. Their scion’s reputation as stalwart mercenaries would quickly gain the attention of the Calradian Empire. Promoted to lead a Vlandian auxiliary company, the dey Fortes would fight alongside the Calradian legions from the frigid lands of the north to the deserts of the Nahasa, becoming a leader among their people. This clout has served the dey Fortes well, and now they sit at the head of the nascent kingdom’s war council and rule over a substantial estate around the Llyn Modris."
	         banner_key="11.71.14.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.141.15.0.450.450.764.754.0.0.0.301.15.0.450.450.764.914.0.0.90.301.15.0.450.450.764.614.0.0.270"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_6"
	         name="{=vbLAA0RF}dey Valant"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_20"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_6_text}The dey Valant are one of the most prestigious of the Vlandian noble houses, claiming descent from Wilund the Bold - or Valandion - himself. Whilst there are few who take this claim seriously, there is nobody who dares to deny their vast wealth and influence over Vlandian society. Instead of signing on to fighting for the Calradian Empire, the dey Valant preferred to remain in their secluded mountain estate on the Ebor Peninsula, monopolizing the trade flowing from southern Calradia to the Nords across the sea to the north. Whilst some have condemned this as an act of cowardice, the wealth of the dey Valant has always bought their obeisance."
	         banner_key="11.71.14.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.336.15.0.400.400.764.814.0.0.0.219.15.0.200.200.764.564.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_8"
	         name="{=9NWQNInC}dey Molarn"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_24"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_8_text}The dey Molarn are the noble house of the city of Ostican – one of the earliest enclaves of the Vlandians on the continent of Calradia. Their ancestors were fortunate, being brought on as servants to the Calradian rulers of the town at the time. Known for their cunning, they proved indispensable to the Calradian Empire, being given the administration of the town when their masters fell out of the graces of the imperial court. The dey Molarn have since amassed a sizeable fortune through the trade of uncommonly fine thoroughbred horses, which today make up the mounts for the majority of the Vlandian cavalry."
	         banner_key="11.14.14.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.315.15.0.450.450.714.764.0.0.50.424.15.0.200.200.764.664.0.0.0.315.15.0.450.450.814.764.0.1.310"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_11"
	         name="{=DeSGiCgF}dey Rothad"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.lord_V11_l"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_11_text}The dey Rothad are renowned across Calradia as one of the most warlike of the Vlandian noble houses, having cut a bloody swathe through friend and foe alike from the southern deserts to the eastern steppe. Descendants of adventurers who settled initially on the Swadian Plains, they were quick to seize on the opportunity for bloodshed and plunder offered by service alongside the legions of the Calradian Empire, encouraging many of their kin to join the imperial forces as auxiliaries. When the Vlandians were transferred back to the western provinces by Emperor Themestios Comnos, the dey Rothad soon grew weary of the reconstruction of Calradian cities, preferring to make war on the Battanians, carving out their own estates on the coast of the Bay of Varcheg."
	         banner_key="11.71.14.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.102.15.0.400.400.764.744.0.0.0.306.15.0.200.300.664.944.0.0.90.306.15.0.200.300.864.944.0.1.-90"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_2_name}dey Hongar"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_3"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_2_text}The dey Hongar are the noble house of Ethenbold - uncle to the first Vlandian king - Osric 'Iron-Arm'. Whilst many may think this relationship would afford the dey Hongar a position of primacy within the nascent Vlandian Kingdom, it is in fact far from the truth. Viewed as little more than useful vassals by Osric, the dey Hongar were assigned the thankless task of maintaining the encirclement of the Calradian city of Paravenos, losing countless men and resources in the years-long process. Nearly bankrupted into obscurity by their task, they resent the authority those ‘wayward’ members of the dey Meroc, considering themselves a better candidate for leadership of the Vlandian people."
	         banner_key="11.101.75.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.140.39.0.300.300.764.784.0.1.0.500.39.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0.424.39.0.200.100.614.764.0.1.90.424.39.0.200.100.914.764.0.0.270.304.39.0.200.300.838.692.0.0.-1"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_10"
	         name="{=yQcZrUYi}dey Folcun"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_28"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_10_text}The dey Folcun, like many Vlandian noble houses, claim their origins in the rough back streets and shady alleyways of the Calradian city of Ostican. Their ancestors were destitute travellers, bartering passage on trading vessels in return for manual labor or a period of domestic servitude. Seeing the potential of their new homeland, the dey Folcun elected to live a hard life on the Battanian frontier in the Rhennod Mountains, fighting off raiding warbands to keep their meager holdings. Today, they are hailed as one of the great bulwarks of the nascent Vlandian Kingdom, protecting the productive lands of the Swadian Plains and Ebor Peninsula from their less savory neighbors."
	         banner_key="11.71.14.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.305.15.0.444.444.759.762.0.0.0.206.15.0.480.480.653.760.0.0.17.206.15.0.480.480.872.768.0.0.194"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_5"
	         name="{=9qAUWcfa}dey Gunric"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_21"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_5_text}The dey Gunric are relatively unique amongst the noble houses of Vlandia. Their ancestors were Nords, who centuries ago ventured across the frigid northern seas to settle on the Ebor Peninsula. Formidable warriors, it was not long before the people of the region came to respect their rule. Quick to intermarry with the successive waves of Vlandian settlers who came to reside in the area around the town of Ostican, the dey Gunric soon cast off many of their Nordic traditions in favor of new Vlandian customs. Zealous supporters of Vlandian independence from the Calradian Empire, they jumped at the opportunity to join the nascent kingdom of Osric 'Iron-Arm'."
	         banner_key="11.14.14.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.418.15.0.300.300.764.864.0.0.0.159.15.0.500.500.764.644.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_9"
	         name="{=LygSwU3i}dey Jelind"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_27"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vlandia"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_9_text}The dey Jelind hail from the Biscan Hills - the westernmost mountain range in Calradia. Their ancestors were mercenaries, who sailed to the continent from the islands to the west in search of fame and riches. Quick to join the service of the Calradian Empire, the scions of the dey Jelind fought against all manner of foes, from the nomads of the east and south to savage raiders from the north, only returning to their western homeland within living memory. When the Emperor Themestios Comnos transferred the Vlandians back to protect the western provinces, the dey Jelind soon found themselves ruling over a small estate on the eastern slopes of the Biscan Hills, near the very place their ancestors once dwelt. They zealously protect this land, and so were quick to join the nascent Vlandian Kingdom."
	         banner_key="11.71.14.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.335.15.0.500.500.764.754.0.0.0.336.15.0.200.200.764.724.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Spahanfar Satrapy
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_1_name}Spahanfar"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_1"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_1_text}The Spahanfar hail from the western borderlands of the lands of the Padishah, having been counted among the most staunch defenders of the Darshi Empire for centuries. During the campaign of the Padishah Hoshtar into the Devseg over three hundred years ago, the Spahanfar first gained an introduction to the lands of Calradia, seeing its vast wealth and potential. Nearly a century later, led by the ambitious general Kourosh, the Spahanfar returned to these western lands, carving a realm from the grasslands of the Devseg down to the sands of the Nahasa. Given authority to fly the Padishah’s banner in rulership over their own satrapy in eastern Calradia, the Spahanfari shahs have since found themselves constantly looking to both preserve their own borders, and expand their influence over the continent."
	         banner_key="11.38.0.4000.4000.776.777.1.0.0.144.1.0.450.450.759.764.0.0.0.119.1.0.200.201.744.668.0.0.-130.500.1.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.560.580.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_2_name}Dhami"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_5"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_2_text}The Dhami are one of the most influential noble families of the Spahanfar Satrapy. Once, their ancestors held a seat on the council of the Padishah, advising the rulers of the Darshi Empire on matters of state. However, the Dhami would come unstuck when one of their more zealous scions was caught in the chambers of a padishah’s daughter, resulting in the entire family being publicly shamed for their digressions and exiled to the western borderlands. Cunning politics and a keen eye for commerce has since seen the restoration of the Dhami fortune, as well as much of their influence on Darshi politics, and now there are few who can escape their machinations within the Satrapy’s borders."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.776.777.1.0.0.401.1.0.507.507.764.764.0.0.359.411.1.0.256.256.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.315.315.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_3_name}Musalan"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_10"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_3_text}The Musalan are a clan of mercenaries from the far southern protectorates of the Darshi Padishah. Seventy years ago, at the request of the Spahanfari Shah, the Musalan were dispatched by the Padishah to aid in the fighting in the Nahasa, decisively turning the tide against the Aserai in a battle before the walls of Razih. Whilst the campaign would ultimately end in the Darshi ignominiously retreating from their conquests under a ferocious Aserai resistance, the Musalan were rewarded for their bravery by the Spahanfari with rulership over the town of Baghkuk. They now form the cornerstone of the Darshi borderlands with the Nahasa, repelling increasingly spirited incursions by their Aserai neighbors."
	         banner_key="11.38.0.4000.4000.776.777.1.0.0.144.1.0.450.450.759.764.0.0.0.119.1.0.200.201.744.668.0.0.-130.500.1.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.560.580.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_4_name}Askapour"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_18"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_4_text}The Askapour are an old and esteemed Darshi family, ruling a small shahdom in the lands around the southern foothills of the Devseg Plateau since the time before the coming of the Padishah's Empire to the east of Calradia. Unlike many of their fellows, the Askapour willingly joined the Darshi Empire following Hoshtar's invasion into the region, becoming prominent warlords in the Padishah's westernmost borderlands. Though now subservient to the Spahanfar Satrapy, their wealth, accumulated over countless generations, gives them substantial leverage within the court of the Shah, and the fruits of their ambitions can readily be seen."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.321.1.0.300.300.764.824.0.0.0.110.1.0.400.400.764.694.0.0.0.521.1.0.174.174.764.544.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_5"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_5_name}Khwarasani"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_22"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_5_text}The Khwarasani claim descent from one of the cadet branches of the line of the Padishah Kavad - their progenitor born of the union of the Darshi ruler and one of his concubines. Despite this familial connection, they were not afforded a high station in Darshi society, being sent to administer a borderland region far from the center of power - and far from the shame of Kavad. The Khwarasani were fast to support the Spahanfari in their incursion into the Nahasa, leading one of the divisions that made up their invading army. Rewarded for their diligent conduct, the Khwarasani were given a smallholding on the border of the new satrapy, staunchly defending their realm against marauders from the great bronze desert."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.406.1.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.0.502.1.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.45.502.1.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.0.406.1.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.45"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_6"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_6_name}Aspahbadhan"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_28"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_6_text}The Aspahbadhan, like many of the Darshi marcher families, claim descent from a long lineage of proud warriors, having fought beneath the banner of the Padishah since the ancient days. Indeed, there are few among the nobility of the western borderlands who can boast of so many ancestors who served in the Immortals - the most fearsome division of the Darshi army. This clout has gained the Aspahbadhan a respected position in the Spahanfar Satrapy, being granted lands in the foothills of the Kuh-e Karkas Mountains, on the border with the nascent Aserai Emirates. From their estates, the Aspahbadhan frequently ride forth to do battle with the nomads of the Nahasa, and there are few in Calradia who would deny their experience on the field of battle."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.500.1.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.450.440.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.430.420.764.764.0.0.0.403.1.0.430.420.764.764.0.0.0.411.1.0.250.250.764.759.0.0.0.503.1.0.200.200.764.759.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_7"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_7_name}Gaubari"
	         tier="3"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_32"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_7_text}The Gaubari are one of the lesser houses of the Darshi nobility, having held a low office as one of the courtiers of the padishahs for over five generations. Aspiring of higher offices and zealous to prove themselves in the ebb and flow of Darshi politics, they were eager to join the Spahanfari campaigns into the Nahasa, hiring a small mercenary army to carve for themselves a small holding on the westernmost borderlands of the Darshi incursion into the great bronze desert. Now, the Gaubari have earned themselves a place at the table of the shah, though must fight hard to hold onto all that they have gained."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.500.1.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.222.1.0.450.450.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.0.411.1.0.250.250.764.764.0.0.0.500.1.0.250.250.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_8"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_8_name}Isfandiyar"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_37"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_8_text}The Isfandiyar hail from the Kuh-e Karkas - the 'Mountains of the Vulture' - in the western borderlands of the Spahanfar Satrapy. Their ancestors were humble hillmen, who roamed the foothills along the Nahr al-Kals River, shepherding their flocks of hardy sheep whilst remaining watchful for raiders from the steppe. However, matters would change over three centuries ago, when the Padishah Hoshtar marched his armies into the region. The Isfandiyar were among the first to turn their crooks to swords and axes, and their opposition was so fierce that the Darshi armies were brought to an almost complete standstill in conquering their mountain home. Recognizing their bravery, Hoshtar elevated the Isfandiyar to hold a minor station among the Darshi nobility - a position that they have zealously guarded in the centuries since."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.502.1.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.425.1.0.200.200.764.764.0.0.0.411.1.0.150.150.764.664.0.0.0.411.1.0.150.150.764.864.0.0.0.510.1.0.350.200.884.764.0.0.90.510.1.0.350.200.644.764.0.0.90"/>
	<Faction id="clan_spahad_9"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_9_name}Varaz"
	         tier="2"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_41"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.spahad"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_spahad_9_text}The Varaz can lay claim to one of the least storied histories of any in the Spahanfar Satrapy. In the days before the Darshi expansion into Calradia, the Varaz were simple goatherds dwelling in the Tiagys River basin. Their progenitor was drafted into the service of the Padishah Arshak in his war against the people of the Devseg, winning acclaim for the clan by single-handedly defeating seven steppe lancers in a single battle with just his sling and spear. Awarded a title of minor nobility, the Varaz have since accompanied many of the Darshi incursions into Calradia, and now form one of the key landholders in the Spahanfar Satrapy, protecting the lands of the shahs against all comers."
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.125.1.0.400.400.834.784.0.0.0.125.1.0.400.400.694.784.0.1.0.411.1.0.150.150.764.584.0.0.0.503.1.0.100.100.764.584.0.0.0"/>
	<!-- 
	LESSER KINGDOM FACTIONS
	-->
	<!--
	Alkit Khanate
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_alkit_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_1_name}Alkit"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_10_1"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.alkit"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_1_text}The Alkit tribe have the misfortune of being the rulers of the most despised realm in all Calradia - not that they have time to care. The Alkit are nomads at heart, bred in the yurt and honed in the saddle into some of the most hardened warriors on the continent. It was a combination of their insatiable bloodlust and greed that drove them to accept the Calradian Empire’s contract to retake the colony of Varnapolys from Nordic raiders, and it was the same bloodlust and greed that led them to seize it for themselves. Now, over half a century after the formation of their Khanate, the Alkit find themselves facing enemies from all sides, and it remains to be seen if their hubris will go unpunished."
	         banner_key="11.25.10.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.427.11.11.400.400.764.923.1.0.0.129.11.11.300.300.759.694.1.0.0.340.11.11.200.200.764.484.1.0.0.504.11.11.90.90.718.476.1.0.-40.504.11.11.90.90.810.477.1.0.39.410.11.11.113.113.764.879.1.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_alkit_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_2_name}Yanait"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_10_5"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.alkit"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_2_text}The Yanait tribe were one of the first to join the Alkit in riding west, cutting a swathe through Nords, Sturgians and Vakken alike, until they reached the walls of the town of Tyal. A pragmatic people, rather than attempting to take the town by force, the Yanait resorted to diplomacy, negotiating the marriage of their daughters into the local aristocracy in exchange for rulership. Whilst this displeased the other, more warlike tribes of the Alkit invasion, none can deny that the Yanait rule over one of the most compliant regions in the nascent Khanate."
	         banner_key="11.25.10.4345.4345.776.778.1.0.0.428.5.5.500.500.764.709.0.1.0.115.5.5.300.300.796.651.0.1.0.426.5.5.300.300.764.963.0.1.90.503.5.5.88.88.686.702.0.1.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_alkit_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_3_name}Khionit"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_10_10"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.alkit"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_3_text}The Khionit, like many of their kin from the eastern steppe, see little point in claiming an origin in any one place or people, instead viewing the saddle as their only home. Infamous for their cruelty, matched only by their cunning, they are known to the other tribes of the Iltanlar as kin-slayers. Half a century ago, the Khionit ruthlessly butchered another neighboring tribe, killing fellow Iltanlar men, women and children in a dispute over grazing lands for their wandering horse herds. Cast out by the Iltanlar Khan for their actions, the Khionit saw fresh opportunities in the lands of the Alkit, turning their terror on the inhabitants of the frozen northern lands."
	         banner_key="11.25.10.4345.4345.776.776.1.0.0.446.5.5.661.661.764.764.0.1.0.128.5.5.200.200.764.764.0.1.0.306.5.5.200.300.604.754.0.0.0.306.5.5.200.300.924.754.0.1.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_alkit_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_4_name}Adiskhar"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_10_15"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.alkit"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_alkit_4_text}The Adiskhar are a relatively obscure tribe of the Alkit Khanate. Known to the people of the Calradian Empire by the derogatory name ‘swamp nomads’, they have dwelt on the edge of the Iltan Portages for centuries, grazing their horse herds on the meager patches of grassland in between the marshes. An unambitious people, and one of the most settled of the Iltanlar, they used the Alkit invasion to seize the nearby castle of Urikskala, displacing the Vakken inhabitants and taking it as their new home. Now, they rule over the Iltan Portages with a vengeance, jealously guarding the festering bogs and hidden pools of their homeland against all comers."
	         banner_key="11.25.10.4345.4345.776.776.1.0.0.500.5.5.450.450.764.710.0.1.0.143.5.5.400.400.757.710.0.1.0.427.5.5.400.268.764.945.0.1.0.411.5.5.88.88.764.579.0.1.0"/>
	<!--
	Byalic Confederation
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_jokbyalic_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_1_name}Suomalai"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_13_1"
	         culture="Culture.byalic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.byals"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_1_text}The Suomalai are the most powerful of the Byalic noble families, having held the high chieftain's throne for centuries. Once, they held a small but wealthy holding along the shoreline of the upper Karakaz River, raising livestock and profiting off the trade of amber and furs from Nordic wanderers to the khans of the Sulun Dag Mountains. The coming of the Nachaghan hordes saw the destruction of the Suomalai’s halls and the death of their high chieftain and nearly his entire bloodline. Saved from destruction only by the swift actions of Fidhr - brother of the former high chieftain - who foresaw their destruction and led his family and retinue westwards, the Suomalai now attempt to rebuild their shattered realm along the frigid coast of the Byalic Sea."
	         banner_key="11.2.38.2000.2000.764.764.1.0.0.408.2.38.509.509.764.764.1.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_jokbyalic_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_2_name}Karzali"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_13_5"
	         culture="Culture.byalic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.byals"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_2_text}The Karzali, like many among the Byals, hail from the sheltered lands between the Karakaz River and the Byalic Sea. The descendants of proud farmer-soldiers who loyally served the ruling Suomalai high chieftains for innumerable centuries, they were among the first to face the incoming Nachaghan hordes - their warriors valiantly holding the line against the rampaging nomads to buy time for their people to escape to the west. Driven nearly to extinction by the Nachaghan, the Karzali now find themselves dwelling now in the rich lands of the former eastern provinces of the Calradian Empire, hoping the high walls may shelter them against the thundering hooves of the east."
	         banner_key="11.7.7.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.416.12.12.450.450.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_jokbyalic_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_3_name}Hamalai"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_13_11"
	         culture="Culture.byalic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.byals"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_3_text}The Hamalai tribe hail from the coastal plains to the southeast of the Byalic Sea. In centuries past, their ancestors eked out a meager existence from fishing the frigid waters, earning enough to construct a smallholding. Their fortunes would change when, just over a century ago, Nordic traders arrived on their shores, transforming the Hamalai’s smallholding into a bustling port trading salt and dried fish with the Nords in exchange for furs and amber. However, the arrival of the Nachaghan hordes saw the lands of the Hamalai devastated by marauding horsemen. Now, they must fight for survival, reluctantly turning from the fishing net to the axe and sword."
	         banner_key="11.7.7.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.500.12.12.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.415.12.12.450.450.764.764.0.0.45"/>
	<Faction id="clan_jokbyalic_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_4_name}Ilvonen"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_13_15"
	         culture="Culture.byalic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.byals"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_jokbyalic_4_text}The Ilvonen hail from the region west of the Doga Karakya - the so-called ‘Black Mountain’ where the Karakaz River meets the frigid tundra of north-eastern Calradia. Proud warriors trained in the arts of mounted warfare, the Ilvonen fared better than many of their kin against the Nachaghan hordes, carving through the ranks of the nomads in a desperate flight to the south. These same horsemen would then win infamy for themselves in battle against the Calradian Empire, single-handedly cutting through the cataphract bodyguards of the Emperor Themestios Comnos and leaving the field with the Emperor’s head. Such feats have earned the Ilvonen a reputation as some of the fiercest warriors in Calradia, though it remains to be seen if even they can keep the Byalic people from falling to their many foes."
	         banner_key="11.7.7.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.437.12.12.450.450.764.754.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Massa Confederation
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_3_name}Armingar"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_5"
	         culture="Culture.massa"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.massa"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_3_text}The Armingar are the wealthiest and most powerful of the Massa tribal families, having wandered the western lands of Calradia for over a century. A nomadic people, their ancestry is shadowed in mystery. Indeed, if one asks any group of the Armingar where their ancestors were from, they will invariably get different answers from everyone. What is known, however, is that wherever they have decided to settle, death and horror follow with them. They run their estates with ruthless efficiency, turning the once peaceful backwater villages of the western provinces of the Calradian Empire into slave farms, exploiting the land and its people until both are spent, before moving on. In this way, the Armingar have amassed for themselves great wealth and power, and there are few in Calradia who would be foolish enough to stand against them."
	         banner_key="11.14.14.4922.4922.580.740.1.0.0.218.15.0.373.373.764.684.0.0.0.220.15.0.184.184.898.898.0.0.357.220.15.0.184.184.630.898.0.0.3.505.15.0.20.184.764.898.0.1.180"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vlandia_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_4_name}Hathdar"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_16"
	         culture="Culture.massa"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.massa"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vlandia_4_text}The Hathdar, like many of their Massa kin, are a mysterious people. According to some Calradian scholars, their ancestors first appeared on the shores of the Biscan Coast sometime after Wilund the Bold - progenitor of the Vlandians - ravaging the local imperial villages and badly mauling a legionary detachment sent to stop them. To stop their incessant pillaging, the Calradian Empire was quick to offer the Hathdar a contract to fight as imperial auxiliaries, paying them an exorbitant amount of gold so that they might migrate into the Rhennod Hills, on the border with the territories of the Battanians. Constant war with raiding Battanian warbands has given the Hathdar centuries to hone their skills on the battlefield - an attribute they have now turned against their former Calradian overlords, along with the rest of their kin."
	         banner_key="11.14.14.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.307.15.0.400.420.814.764.0.1.-30.207.15.0.200.200.664.764.0.0.50.220.15.0.100.100.764.620.0.0.0.307.15.0.400.420.714.764.0.0.30.207.15.0.200.200.864.764.0.1.310"/>
	<Faction id="clan_massa_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_massa_1_name}Marynd"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_11_1"
	         culture="Culture.massa"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.massa"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_massa_1_text}The Marynd are one of the lesser tribal families of the Massa Confederation, having only seized and settled in the fortifications of Cheleas Castle in recent years. Their ancestors were Vlandians, who refused the call of the Calradian Empire to serve in one of its eastern wars and fled into the forests of the west, living as common bandits until they found safe haven amongst a wandering Massa caravan. Skilled in the art of mounted warfare, they were the ones to introduce the Massa to horse-riding, transforming the crude warbands of their people into effective armies, capable of fighting on par with the vaunted Calradian legions. Zealous in battle, as well as at the negotiating table, the Marynd are a force to be reckoned with, and many in Calradia only speak their names in hushed tones, lest they taste of their sharp steel."
	         banner_key="11.12.12.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.218.40.127.500.500.764.744.0.0.0.301.40.127.500.500.764.984.0.0.-90.301.40.127.500.500.764.984.0.1.90.521.40.127.100.100.764.524.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_massa_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_massa_2_name}Gosardth"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_11_6"
	         culture="Culture.massa"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.massa"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_massa_2_text}The Gosardth have the reputation of being the most cruel and destructive of the Massa tribal families. It is believed by some that their ancestors were Nords, whose wayward travels saw them land on Vesperos - the 'Evening Isle' - that lies off the western coast of Calradia. Unlike many of their Massa kin, they did not take an auxiliary contract with the Calradian Empire, instead being simply shepherded by the Calradian legions into the Rhennod Hills, so that they might fight the Battanians rather than imperial forces. They were quick to join their kin in revolt, carving a bloody path across the western provinces of the Calradian Empire until they had returned to the island of Vesperos, constructing a small hillfort and enslaving the islanders. Now, the Gosardth look east from their island home, daring any on the mainland to oppose them."
	         banner_key="11.12.12.2000.2000.764.764.1.0.0.347.40.127.300.300.764.714.0.1.0.206.40.127.300.300.654.814.0.0.45.206.40.127.300.300.874.814.0.1.315.220.40.127.100.100.764.894.0.1.0"/>
	<!--
	Quyazic Empire
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_quyaz_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_1_name}Naumatos"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_9_1"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.quyaz"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_1_text}The Naumatos family have called the lands around the town of Quyaz home for centuries. Originally descended from Calradian colonists who settled in the area following the defeat of the Quyazic by the Calradian Republic, the Naumatos built a reputation as steadfast mariners and canny merchants. Leveraging connections with the Calradian nobility at Charasea, the Naumatos soon came to monopolize the formerly-Quyazic trade routes across the Perassic Sea, trading in dates and spices from the eastern Nahasa. Whilst not completely trusted by the old Kannic families of Quyaz, they have nonetheless come to dominate the politics of the town, ensuring its rise from a formerly defeated power to one which may again challenge others for supremacy over Calradia."
	         banner_key="11.72.72.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.333.5.0.300.300.749.729.0.0.0.423.5.0.507.507.764.751.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_quyaz_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_2_name}Magonos"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_9_5"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.quyaz"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_2_text}The Magonos descend from a long and storied line of Kannic aristocrats who have called the town of Aradiyaz home since the very first days of its founding. Ruling over the great breadbasket of the far western Nahasa, their estates have long been seen as the most essential component of any attempt to gain control over the Nahasa, feeding armies from both east and west in their campaigns across the great bronze desert. After the Quyazic Wars, the Magonos family was shown mercy by the victorious Calradian Republic, being allowed to rebuild their estates in exchange for providing a tribute of grain to Charasea every year. Staunch believers in an resurgence of Kannic culture, they have seized the opportunity of the Calradian civil war to fight for their independence."
	         banner_key="11.72.72.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.500.5.0.507.507.764.751.0.0.0.500.5.0.425.425.763.752.0.0.0.201.5.0.350.350.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_quyaz_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_3_name}Geranos"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_9_9"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.quyaz"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_3_text}The Geranos, like many other families dwelling in the western Nahasa, are at the crossroads of two worlds. Descendants of Calradian colonists who married into the local Kannic population, the Geranos made their fame and fortune in the cultivation of fine olives. Indeed, oil from their estates in the Lysian highlands may be found on the tables of Kings, Emperors and Khans from the Biscan Coast to the Devseg - a feat that has made them one of the most renowned families of farmers on the continent. Supporters of the aristocracy in the nearby town of Quyaz, the Geranos now mobilize their wealth and power in support of the adoptive homeland."
	         banner_key="11.72.72.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.208.5.0.350.350.764.754.0.0.0.202.5.5.550.446.669.764.0.1.-95.202.5.5.550.450.859.764.0.0.95"/>
	<Faction id="clan_quyaz_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_4_name}Barcoses"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_9_13"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.quyaz"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_quyaz_4_text}The Barcoses family can claim descent from one of the greatest lineages of the old Kannic nobility. In the days before the Quyazic Wars, they held the honour of presiding over the Senate of Quyaz for over six consecutive generations, leading their people in matters of state and warfare. Following their defeat at the hands of the Calradian Empire, the Barcoses were exiled to their estates near Uqba, on the Perassic Sea, never to hold office in the Calradian provincial administration at Quyaz again. However, following the secession of the Quyazic Empire, the Barcoses now see an opportunity to regain their lost power and status, re-joining the political order they once led."
	         banner_key="11.72.72.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.450.5.0.300.300.764.734.0.0.0.502.5.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.45.518.5.0.150.150.944.584.0.0.90.518.5.0.150.150.584.584.0.0.90.518.5.0.150.150.584.944.0.0.90.518.5.0.150.150.944.944.0.0.90"/>
	<!--
	Tanash City States
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_tanash_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_1_name}Zarinzadeh"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_14_1"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.tanash"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_1_text}The Zarinzadeh are the oldest and most powerful family from the Tanash city state of Makeb, claiming descent from merchants who originally set up their caravan to sell their wares on what would become the site of the city. Whilst not a martial people, they have survived for centuries through cunning and the liberal application of their wealth, buying the support of the common people, and the silence of their foes. Whilst it is unlikely any of their family shall prove formidable in combat, their political machinations make them a serious threat to any who would wish to cross the interests of Makeb."
	         banner_key="11.61.154.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.216.137.0.450.450.764.774.0.0.180.427.137.0.200.100.759.994.0.0.0.342.137.0.100.100.764.504.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_tanash_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_2_name}Esbarafar"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_14_7"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.tanash"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_2_text}The Esbarafar hail from the Tanash city state of Chaikand, having migrated there only two generations ago from the Empire of the Padishah to seek their fortune in the trade of luxury goods from Calradia into the Darshi homeland. Demonstrating a particularly cut-throat approach to commerce, they have rapidly established themselves as one of the most prominent families in Chaikand, and now speak on behalf of the city in councils with representatives from other Tanashi cities. The Esbarafar have been a vocal proponent of Tanashi independence, wishing to throw off Calradian rule for closer ties with the Darshi Empire."
	         banner_key="11.61.154.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.337.137.0.400.400.764.769.0.0.0.411.137.0.200.200.764.654.0.0.0.500.137.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_tanash_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_3_name}Sowdafar"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_14_17"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.tanash"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_3_text}The Sowdafar are a common cautionary tale of the Tanashi lands of eastern Calradia. These lands have seen the rise and fall of many great families, from beggared merchants to once-reputed politicians cast into obscurity. Once the rulers of a petty shahdom around the ancient Darshi fortress city of Akkalat, six decades ago, the Sowdafar were caught off-guard by the most recent westward expansion of the Spahanfar Satrapy. Forced to watch from their battlements as the invaders carved up much of their former estates into a new satrapy for the Padishah, the Sowdafar now find themselves without the source of their wealth and power. They resent the authority of the Padishah, and await the day that they might reclaim their former lands."
	         banner_key="11.154.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.500.11.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.119.11.0.200.200.764.774.0.0.0.521.11.0.100.100.764.624.0.0.0.321.11.0.300.100.764.920.0.0.0.221.11.0.100.100.634.764.0.0.0.221.11.0.100.100.894.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_tanash_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_4_name}Uzitsana"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_14_14"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.tanash"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_tanash_4_text}The Uzitsana hail from the mountain village of Akiser, set high on the slopes of the Akkan Hills in a key pass between the Tanash city states and the Devseg Plateau. The descendants of mercenaries from the steppe, who fought for the Tanashi in one of their many wars against the nomads of the Devseg, the Uzitsana were rewarded for their service with lordship over the borderlands. They are highly prized by the mercantile Tanashi for both their prowess in battle and at the negotiating table, ensuring the passivity of the neighboring steppe tribes and the protection of the precious trade caravans from the east."
	         banner_key="11.1.0.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.137.1.0.400.400.744.784.0.0.0.137.1.0.400.400.784.784.0.1.0.521.1.0.180.180.764.614.0.1.0"/>
	<!--
	Vaegir Kingdom
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_vaegiria_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_1_name}Vagiraving"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_8_1"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vaegiria"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_1_text}The Vagiraving - the ‘House of the Companions’ - are one of the most ancient Vakken noble families, having dwelt in the dark forests of the Ircara Wildlands since the time before the coming of Calradios the Great to the continent. They are a lineage of warrior farmers, whose ancestors raised the great fortress town of Omor where the forest meets the shoreline of Lake Laconis, earning great wealth and status in Vakken society. Throughout the history of Calradia, whenever the boyars of the Vakken met to take counsel, the Vagiraving held the position of high esteem. Unsurprisingly, this meant the Vagiraving were swift to take the crown following the independence of their people, coming to rule over a realm precariously sited on the edges of the Calradian Empire."
	         banner_key="11.33.33.4000.4000.776.778.1.0.0.306.148.148.312.479.770.930.0.1.-90.503.148.148.124.126.765.619.0.1.90.144.148.148.441.407.773.803.0.1.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vaegiria_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_2_name}Kaldaving"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_8_5"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vaegiria"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_2_text}The Kaldaving hail from the frigid foothills of the Chertyg Mountains, having only migrated to the Vaegir heartland of the Ircara Wildlands within the past three generations. Once, they were simple woodsmen, growing their wealth and status in Calradian society through the trade of furs and amber from the dark northern forests. However, years of nearly constant conflict with Nordic raiders has hardened them into some of the finest warriors on the continent. Naturally, this made them prime candidates for border guards of the Calradian Empire, earning for them a small estate in the northern borderlands. Now, with the Vaegirs declaring themselves to be an independent realm, the Kaldaving find themselves once again turning to the art of war."
	         banner_key="11.33.33.4000.4000.776.778.1.0.0.309.148.148.312.479.764.949.0.0.241.220.148.148.150.150.765.599.0.1.0.145.148.148.400.300.784.774.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vaegiria_3"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_3_name}Dervoving"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_8_10"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vaegiria"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_3_text}The Dervoving claim descent from a long line of merchants and adventurers, having dwelt on the western the fringes of the Ircara Wildlands since the days of the Calradian Republic. However, whilst many other Vakken families have risen to prominence throughout the centuries from their involvement in commerce or warfare, the Dervoving have had no such luck. Instead, their estate’s precarious location on the fringe of the Cursion Escarpment has resulted in a nearly constant state of conflict with Battanian raiders. Many times has the wealth and status of the Dervoving been torn down by marauding hillmen, making them one of the most embattled peoples in Calradia."
	         banner_key="11.35.35.4000.4000.776.778.1.0.0.426.148.148.137.129.687.578.0.0.0.306.148.148.311.391.764.943.0.1.-90.129.148.148.310.300.748.795.0.0.359.515.148.148.105.100.804.544.0.0.0.515.148.148.81.77.872.602.0.0.0.515.148.148.67.63.817.646.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_vaegiria_4"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_4_name}Sarapisthes"
	         tier="4"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_8_17"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.vaegiria"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_vaegiria_4_text}The Sarapisthes, unlike many among the Vaegir Kingdom, are not actually members of the Vakken people. They are in fact Calradians, hailing from their fortified estates of Mecalovea, overlooking the frigid waters of Lake Laconis. A marriage pact with one of the Vakken noble families has seen their eldest daughter and her heirs placed in line to one of the most prosperous of the northern fur trading emporiums, though not without cost. With the Calradian Empire in crisis, the Sarapisthes have chosen the bonds of kin over their allegiance to the Emperor, and so now fight for the Vaegirs against their own people."
	         banner_key="11.35.35.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.411.148.148.92.87.764.532.0.0.0.426.148.148.311.391.764.943.0.1.-90.100.148.148.350.350.764.744.0.0.359"/>
	<!-- 
	MINOR KINGDOM FACTIONS
	-->
	<!--
	Amprela Archontate
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_amprela_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_amprela_1_name}Kamytzes"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_18_1"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.amprela"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_amprela_1_text}The Kamytzes are the current ruling family of the Calradian colony town of Amprela. Their ancestors hailed from the eastern steppe, pledging their service to the Calradian Empire in exchange for safe lands behind the imperial frontiers. Over the following generations, the Kamytzes have loyally protected the eastern borders against all manner of foes, from the ferocious warriors of the north to the marauding horsemen of the steppe, to the disciplined divisions of the Darshi. They have strong connection with the Eleftheroi freemen, and a scion of the Kamytzes can often be seen riding at the head of their horde. Now, with the Calradian Empire descending into civil war, the Kamytzes have decided to chart their own course, denying the summons of Solarios and his rebel empire to look to the interests of their own people."
	         banner_key="11.133.133.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.90.126.5.5.300.300.764.744.0.0.0.423.5.5.500.500.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_amprela_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_amprela_2_name}Axouchos"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_18_7"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.amprela"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_amprela_2_text}The Axouchos, like many noble families inhabiting the eastern provinces of the Calradian Empire, cannot claim descent from an ancient lineage of the Calradic people. They are descendants of the Palaic peoples of the Myzead - the hill country that separates the plains of central Calradia from the wild lands of the east. Seeing the fate of those who resisted the legions, their ancestors were quick to submit to imperial authority, being allowed to maintain their estates in the new eastern borderlands in exchange for defending them against the foes of the Calradian Empire. A martial people, bound by a strict code of honor, they tentatively joined the rebellion of Solarios ‘Light-Giver’, though quickly came to resent his cruelty and brutality. When their Empress was put to death, the Axouchos were one of the few who protested, swearing obeisance to the Archon of Amprela instead. Branded as traitors by Solarios’ regime, they now must follow their own path, to whatever end."
	         banner_key="11.133.133.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.90.316.5.5.300.300.764.784.0.0.0.500.5.5.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.523.5.5.100.100.764.614.0.0.0.202.5.5.399.300.869.814.0.0.69.202.5.5.399.300.659.814.0.1.290"/>
	<!--
	Geroian Republic
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_geroianys_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_geroianys_1_name}Hamilakes"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_17_1"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.geroianys"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_geroianys_1_text}The Hamilakes hail from the island of Perassis Major, in the center of the Perassic Sea. Their ancestors were Kannic explorers, who sailed west from their homeland of Razih in search of land to claim as their own, coming to found a small haven on the coast of the largest island that they charted. Over the centuries, the Hamilakes grew their wealth through commerce, monopolizing the trade routes passing between the Kannic cites of Razih and Quyaz. When the latter lost to the ever-expanding Calradians, the Hamilakes sensed the change on the wind, and so submitted to the nascent Calradian Empire without a fight, being allowed to maintain their dominance over the Perassic in exchange for providing the Calradians with their ships and much of their wealth. Now, with their island a sleepy imperial backwater, and their Calradian overlords in civil crisis, the Hamilakes must chart their own path in the turbulent waters."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.521.11.0.100.100.764.564.0.0.0.328.11.0.300.350.764.764.0.1.0.423.11.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_geroianys_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_geroianys_2_name}Geskonos"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_17_7"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.geroianys"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_geroianys_2_text}The Geskonos are one of the most ancient noble houses of the Perassic Sea, having called the island of Perassis Major home since the days of the great Quyazic Republic. In centuries past, they made their name as skilled mariners, sailing their fleets across the calm, shallow waters to raid both the northern and southern coasts of the great sea, exacting tribute from Calradians, Kannics and Palaics alike, lest their sails appear over the horizon. Indeed, when the islands eventually fell under Calradian control, the new lords of the Perassic were eager to put the skills of the Geskonos to use, and so their fleet became an integral part of the Calradian navy. However, with their dominance assured and few to fight in the Perassic Sea, the Calradians were quick to divert funds and support away from their navy, and so the Geskonos saw their power and influence gradually decline. Today, their mighty fleet has passed into legend, spoken often by old fishermen in their taverns, but little noticed in the halls of power."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.521.11.0.100.100.764.544.0.0.0.458.11.0.300.300.764.764.0.0.0.423.11.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Paravenos Archontate
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_paravenos_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_paravenos_1_name}Akropolites"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_16_1"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.paravenos"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_paravenos_1_text}The Akropolites - the ‘family of the sacred city’ – have been the rulers of the city of Paravenos since the days of Calradian Kingdom. Descended from the first steward of Calradios the Great, it was the Akropolites who paced the sacred boundary of the new western capital, laying out its streets, districts and monumental edifices. Rewarded richly for their toils with power, wealth and status beyond almost any family in the Calradian Empire, recent times have been cruel to the Akropolites. Initially welcoming to the Vlandians and their kin and seeing their value in their industrious and warlike natures, they have since found themselves at the pointy end of Vlandian independence. Now, the ancient capital is surrounded by the former-allies-turned-enemies, and it remains to be seen if the Akropolites will weather the coming storm."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.521.11.0.100.100.764.564.0.0.0.328.11.0.300.350.764.764.0.1.0.423.11.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_paravenos_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_paravenos_2_name}Rendakis"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_16_8"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.paravenos"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_paravenos_2_text}The Rendakis, unlike many noble families of the western provinces of the Calradian Empire, cannot claim descent from a long and illustrious line of the Calradian nobility. Their ancestors were minor nobles of the Palaic people of the Myzead - the hill country in the east of the Calradian Empire. When the legions came, the Rendakis wisely bowed to imperial authority, and so were allowed to keep their wealth and status, despite being dispossessed of their lands. Migrating to the western provinces, when those lands were considered little more than a sleepy imperial backwater, they built for themselves a pleasant life running a vineyard on the plains east of Paravenos. However, with the rise of the nascent Vlandian Kingdom, the Rendakis now find themselves called upon to defend their very way of life, lest it go extinct."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.104.11.0.300.350.764.774.0.1.0.500.11.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	Yachios Archontate
	-->
	<Faction id="clan_yachios_1"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_yachios_1_name}Carasios"
	         tier="6"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_15_1"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.yachios"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_yachios_1_text}The Carasios family, known to their Aserai neighbors as the ‘Banu Qaraz’, are one of the oldest families of the Calradian Empire. Originally hailing from the port city of Charasea, they were among the marcher archons who joined Emperor Mavinon’s campaign into the Nahasa, founding the outpost of Yachios to guard the borderlands of the Calradian Empire’s Nahasan provinces. The growth of their lands from military fort to thriving cosmopolitan town has brought much wealth and power to the Carasios. However, with the growing assertiveness of the Aserai, the Carasios have now found themselves cut off from imperial authority, their archontate isolated among shifting sands."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.119.11.0.300.300.764.764.0.1.15.202.11.0.400.300.624.784.0.1.270.202.11.0.400.300.904.784.0.0.90.500.11.0.600.600.764.771.0.0.0"/>
	<Faction id="clan_yachios_2"
	         name="{=si_ar_clan_yachios_2_name}Khalkapatres"
	         tier="5"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_15_8"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         super_faction="Kingdom.yachios"
	         is_noble="true"
	         text="{=si_ar_clan_yachios_2_text}The Khalkapatres are a clear example of both the immense potential and dangers of life on the borderlands of the Calradian Empire. Only two generations ago, they were mere imperial citizens, eking out an existence in the slums of Ortysia. However, their fortunes would change when their then-patriarch Morynon enlisted in the Calradian legions. Rising swiftly through the ranks during the campaigns of the Emperor Zaricos Comnos against the Aserai, the Khalkapatres were awarded a parcel of land around the colony of Yachios for their service. Before long, they had established themselves as an authority in the colony, sitting on the town council and serving with distinction in the town watch. However, with the Aserai now encroaching on all sides, it remains to be seen how long the Khalkapatres’ good fortune may last."
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.341.11.0.400.400.754.664.0.1.0.427.11.0.400.400.764.864.0.0.0"/>
	<!--
	MINOR NOMAD FACTIONS
	-->
	<Faction id="ghilman"
	         initial_posX="360.0"
	         initial_posY="212.0"
	         banner_key="33.154.10.1500.1500.764.764.1.0.0.505.11.11.27.121.838.862.0.0.121.505.11.11.20.121.688.863.0.0.49.505.11.11.110.28.766.892.0.0.0.505.11.11.72.168.766.829.0.0.0.505.11.11.345.28.766.938.0.0.0.205.11.129.345.345.850.725.0.1.8.205.11.129.345.345.681.725.0.0.351.219.126.129.345.345.766.767.0.0.0.218.11.129.185.185.767.668.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FFD0884E"
	         color="FFD0884E"
	         color2="FFD0884E"
	         alternative_color="FFD0884E"
	         alternative_color2="FFD0884E"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_mercenary_aserai_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_ghilman_name}Kolemen"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_ghilman_short_name}Kolemen"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_ghilman_text}The Kolemen are a band of mercenaries who hail from the Darshi lands to the east of Calradia. In an obscure eastern tradition, they are legally their own slaves and masters: each ‘sells’ himself to the order and, in the process, becomes a part-owner. They are known for their fine clothes and excellent horses. However, no one should assume from their oiled locks, perfumes and peacock feathers that they spend more time preening than training. Their skills as mounted archers are second to none, and as lancers they are second only to the cataphracts of the Vlandians or Calradians.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ghilman_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ghilman_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ghilman_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ghilman_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="legion_of_the_betrayed"
	         initial_posX="472.0"
	         initial_posY="372.0"
	         banner_key="11.145.145.1536.1536.764.764.1.0.0.301.40.40.196.196.678.903.0.0.55.301.40.40.196.196.850.904.0.1.304.215.155.155.365.365.764.750.0.1.180.423.129.129.590.590.764.764.0.0.0.340.40.40.144.144.764.534.0.1.0"
	         label_color="FF5C2017"
	         color="FF5C2017"
	         color2="FFECBA44"
	         alternative_color="FF5C2017"
	         alternative_color2="FFECBA44"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_mercenary_empire_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_legion_of_the_betrayed_name}Lost Legion"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_legion_of_the_betrayed_short_name}Legion"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_legion_of_the_betrayed_text}The Calradian Empire's famed Nineth Legion - the 'Jackals of Jalmarys', was raised in the year 636 by Emperor Ecsorios Osticos to serve in the Dryatic Wars. It fought with distinction for centuries, crushing all foes under foot. However, in the year 934 the nineth was marched into the Battanian highlands, never to return. Rumours spread that the legion was cut down by a horde of Battanian hillmen - its officers massacred and standards burned. Those few who survived took to the hills, becoming known as the Lost Legion. Whilst still bearing the arms and armor of a proud imperial legion, these men now fight for none but themselves, carving a bloody swathe across Calradia.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_legion_of_the_betrayed_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_legion_of_the_betrayed_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_legion_of_the_betrayed_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_legion_of_the_betrayed_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="skolderbrotva"
	         initial_posX="530.0"
	         initial_posY="595.0"
	         banner_key="16.12.149.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.111.40.155.297.297.748.730.0.0.0.434.46.155.344.384.559.722.0.0.0.434.46.155.344.384.975.722.0.1.0.438.46.155.330.330.768.952.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF66CCFF"
	         color="FF66CCFF"
	         color2="FF66CCFF"
	         alternative_color="FF66CCFF"
	         alternative_color2="FF66CCFF"
	         culture="Culture.nord"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_mercenary_sturgia_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_skolderbrotva_name}Skolderbroda"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_skolderbrotva_short_name}Skolderbroda"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_skolderbrotva_text}The Skolderbroda, or ‘Shield Brothers’, are a mercenary company hailing from the frozen north. Originally Nordic raiders, drawn to Calradia with dreams of plunder and glory, they have since settled into the role of a traditional Calradian mercenary. Their rules are almost monastic: no women in their encampments and no amusements, and no Brother is allowed to spend the night outside without permission. In combat they fight with spear and axe in the Nordic style and are valued by all the noble houses of the north.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_skolderbrotva_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_skolderbrotva_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_skolderbrotva_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_skolderbrotva_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="company_of_the_boar"
	         initial_posX="167.0"
	         initial_posY="553.0"
	         banner_key="11.148.148.1500.1500.764.764.1.0.0.151.0.155.500.500.764.739.0.0.0.419.155.155.241.241.584.534.0.0.0.424.40.40.241.241.584.994.0.0.0.424.40.40.241.241.944.534.0.0.0.419.155.155.241.241.944.994.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FFAA415D"
	         color="FFAA415D"
	         color2="FFAA415D"
	         alternative_color="FFAA415D"
	         alternative_color2="FFAA415D"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_mercenary_vlandia_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_company_of_the_boar_name}Company of the Golden Boar"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_company_of_the_boar_short_name}Company"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_company_of_the_boar_text}The Company of the Boar originate from an auxiliary unit of the same name which served the Calradian Empire in years past, though now they fight only for the highest bidder. They are probably the least disciplined and most brigandish of Calradia's mercenaries, and a scourge to any land where they are allowed to run loose. Still, like all mercenaries, they know that their future earnings depend on their reputation, so they honor their contracts and practice their skills, particularly with the crossbow, to ensure their employers receive their money's worth.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_company_of_the_boar_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_company_of_the_boar_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_company_of_the_boar_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_company_of_the_boar_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="beni_zilal"
	         initial_posX="445.0"
	         initial_posY="55.0"
	         banner_key="24.7.97.2500.2500.764.764.1.0.0.309.41.0.334.334.777.748.0.0.-45"
	         label_color="FFB38841"
	         color="FFB38841"
	         color2="FFB38841"
	         alternative_color="FFB38841"
	         alternative_color2="FFB38841"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_aserai_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_mafia="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_beni_zilal_name}Beni Zilal"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_beni_zilal_short_name}Beni Zilal"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_beni_zilal_text}The Beni Zilal, or so-called ‘Keepers of the Secret’, are a shadowy order who developed around the taverns and bath-houses of the Aserai. Trading in secrets and lies, it is rumoured the Beni Zilal have made more than one lord of the Nahasa and have been involved in the assassination of many more. However, even the most shadowy of cabal falls in need of coin from time to time, and so a chapter of the Beni Zilal now roam the southern wastes, becoming little more than a tribe of bandits.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_beni_zilal_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_beni_zilal_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_beni_zilal_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_beni_zilal_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="wolfskins"
	         initial_posX="261.0"
	         initial_posY="509.0"
	         banner_key="14.2.95.4000.4000.724.764.1.0.0.412.155.155.200.200.764.564.0.0.0.148.41.0.500.500.754.754.0.0.0.412.155.155.200.200.764.964.0.1.180"
	         label_color="FF848B65"
	         color="FF848B65"
	         color2="FF848B65"
	         alternative_color="FF848B65"
	         alternative_color2="FF848B65"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_battania_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_mafia="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_wolfskins_name}Wolfskins"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_wolfskins_short_name}Wolfskins"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_wolfskins_text}The Wolfskins are heirs to a long tradition in the Battanian lands wherein great warriors went ‘wilding’ for a part of their youth, learning the ways of the woods and how to fight and suffer hardship. So long as a Wolfskin wears the fur of a wolf, eats no cooked food, and sleeps under no roof, he is immune from the laws of men. In fact, the Wolfskins of today tend to be the sons of wealthy families, taking a few years to indulge their feral side by robbing travellers and living viciously, whilst not necessarily adhering to the old code.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_wolfskins_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_wolfskins_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_wolfskins_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_wolfskins_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="brotherhood_of_woods"
	         initial_posX="170.0"
	         initial_posY="414.0"
	         banner_key="3.2.40.1536.1536.764.764.1.0.0.219.155.155.266.266.614.564.0.0.0.418.155.155.234.234.914.564.0.0.0.418.155.155.234.234.614.964.0.0.0.219.155.155.266.266.914.964.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color2="FF5A7A4F"
	         alternative_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         alternative_color2="FF5A7A4F"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_vlandia_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_mafia="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_brotherhood_of_woods_name}Brotherhood of the Woods"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_brotherhood_of_woods_short_name}Brotherhood"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_brotherhood_of_woods_text}The Brotherhood of the Woods began just a generation ago as a Vlandian peasant movement, hiding out in the forests, robbing from rich Calradian merchants and giving the spoils to the poor Vlandian farmers. However, hard times lead to hard measures, and the Brotherhood has recently taken to ‘requisitioning’ food from the very farmers they swore to protect, and now rumors spread of cruel punishments being inflicted in the dead of night on those poor who would dare earn a bag of coins by informing on them. Slowly but surely, they have started to make use of extortion, terror, and corrupt deals with the local authorities to survive, becoming little different from any other organized bandit group in Calradia.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_brotherhood_of_woods_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_brotherhood_of_woods_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_brotherhood_of_woods_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_brotherhood_of_woods_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="hidden_hand"
	         initial_posX="486.0"
	         initial_posY="333.0"
	         banner_key="11.147.147.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.342.155.155.400.400.779.739.0.0.0.340.127.127.121.121.764.502.0.0.0.202.2.2.350.272.867.1045.0.0.0.202.2.2.350.272.660.1045.0.1.0.423.2.2.590.590.764.764.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF66CCFF"
	         color="FF66CCFF"
	         color2="FF66CCFF"
	         alternative_color="FF66CCFF"
	         alternative_color2="FF66CCFF"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_empire_w_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_mafia="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_hidden_hand_name}Hidden Hand"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_hidden_hand_short_name}Hand"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_hidden_hand_text}The Hidden Hand are a mafia who have for centuries dominated the rural areas, and sometimes towns, of the Calradian Empire. They thrive by making themselves useful to authorities: repressing unrest, silencing troublesome preachers, and robbing from merchants who compete with their patrons. Many of them go back and forth between a respectable life in the towns and a criminal life in countryside, spending two or three months every year as a brigand or enforcer, and the rest as a ‘trader’ in stolen goods, knowing full well that no one will bother them.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hidden_hand_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hidden_hand_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hidden_hand_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hidden_hand_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="lakepike"
	         initial_posX="628.0"
	         initial_posY="328.0"
	         banner_key="3.149.12.1536.1536.771.761.1.0.0.347.33.0.281.281.767.658.0.0.359.307.33.0.281.523.910.717.0.1.-17.307.33.0.281.523.619.717.0.0.16.438.33.0.494.494.765.909.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF7CAFC7"
	         color="FF7CAFC7"
	         color2="FF7CAFC7"
	         alternative_color="FF7CAFC7"
	         alternative_color2="FF7CAFC7"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_sturgia_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_mafia="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_lakepike_name}Lake Rats"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_lakepike_short_name}Lake Rats"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_lakepike_text}The Lake Rats live in the marshes on the shores of Lake Laconis, often dwelling in shacks made built from the timbers, sails and cordage of wrecked ships. They live by ‘wrecking’ - a process of luring ships onto shoals with false beacons. Because they are scorned by the rest of Calradia as little more than criminals who ‘smell like marsh gas and mud and rotten fish’, they scorn everyone else back. Although mostly Sturgian, their ranks have been swelled by fugitives, debtors, and anyone else who would rather live by a thieves' code than by the laws of the land.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lakepike_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lakepike_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lakepike_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lakepike_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="embers_of_flame"
	         initial_posX="575.0"
	         initial_posY="446.0"
	         banner_key="11.148.5.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.505.5.148.250.11.756.763.0.0.0.202.5.148.402.402.677.595.0.0.234.202.5.148.402.402.849.599.0.1.123.202.5.148.402.402.677.936.0.1.-55.202.5.148.402.402.850.933.0.0.54.106.5.148.322.322.762.674.0.0.0.321.5.148.270.270.760.860.0.0.0.340.5.148.80.80.760.581.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF7C2B1A"
	         color="FF7C2B1A"
	         color2="FF7C2B1A"
	         alternative_color="FF7C2B1A"
	         alternative_color2="FF7C2B1A"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_empire_e_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_sect="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_embers_of_flame_name}Seekers of Cypegos"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_embers_of_flame_short_name}Seekers"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_embers_of_flame_text}The Seekers of Cypegos are a shadowy quasi-religious cabal of lesser Calradian nobles, mercenaries, revolutionaries and brigands. Meeting in secret, they are bent on a single purpose - to destroy the Calradian Empire and reforge it in the image of Cypegos - the semi-mythical last king of the Calradic Kingdom. It was the Seekers who led Emperor Themestios to his doom in the east, luring the imperial armies ever further away from their fortified border, whilst feeding their enemies information about their movements. Now revealed to the world, the Seekers have chosen to wage an open war against all comers, revealing their nature as little more than bandits.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_embers_of_flame_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_embers_of_flame_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_embers_of_flame_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_embers_of_flame_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="jawwal"
	         initial_posX="692.0"
	         initial_posY="217.0"
	         banner_key="34.154.89.1536.1536.772.768.1.0.0.411.155.0.600.600.764.764.0.0.0.329.40.40.153.153.765.765.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FFAC5F2E"
	         color="FFAC5F2E"
	         color2="FFAC5F2E"
	         alternative_color="FFAC5F2E"
	         alternative_color2="FFAC5F2E"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_jawwal_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_jawwal_name}Jawwal"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_jawwal_short_name}Jawwal"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_jawwal_text}The Jawwal, or ‘Roamers’, are the main bedouin confederacy of the Nahasa Desert. They wander from highland to lowland grazing grounds, droving great flocks of goats and herds of camels, and declaring huge swathes of the desert their ‘territory’ in which any caravan must offer protection money. They compose poems of their deeds and mock other clans of the Banu Asera for having given up the ‘freedom’ of woollen tents and the saddle for stone houses in the oases. The other clans of the Banu Asera consider them boastful nuisances, though grudgingly respecting them as protectors of the old ways of the great bronze desert.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_jawwal_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_jawwal_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_jawwal_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_jawwal_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="karakhuzaits"
	         initial_posX="700.0"
	         initial_posY="515.0"
	         banner_key="34.116.10.1536.1536.772.766.1.0.0.314.40.40.370.370.764.762.0.0.269.500.155.155.480.500.764.764.0.0.269"
	         label_color="FF72583B"
	         color="FF72583B"
	         color2="FF72583B"
	         alternative_color="FF72583B"
	         alternative_color2="FF72583B"
	         culture="Culture.karakhuzait"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_karakhuzaits_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_karakhuzaits_name}Karakhuzait"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_karakhuzaits_short_name}Karakhuzait"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_karakhuzaits_text}The Karakhuzait are a nomadic clan that has recently appeared in the uplands of the Devseg, raiding and trading with the Iltanlar tribes of the region. Whilst the Iltanlar tolerate their strange guttural tongue and unusual customs, the Karakhuzait often find themselves expelled from Iltanlar settlements for fighting or stealing. Despite their crude ways, there are many who believe there are no finer horsemen than the Karakhuzait, nor any more experienced with the bow. Indeed, some who have spent time with the Karakhuzait believe they are in fact not mere savages of the steppe, but the vanguard of a great nomadic people further to the east.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_karakhuzaits_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_karakhuzaits_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_karakhuzaits_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_karakhuzaits_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="forest_people"
	         initial_posX="195.0"
	         initial_posY="399.0"
	         banner_key="34.2.61.1736.1736.768.768.1.0.0.203.27.0.373.373.890.754.0.0.359.203.27.0.373.373.650.757.0.0.359.203.155.0.500.500.778.739.0.0.359.510.27.0.414.330.764.1021.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF61725E"
	         color="FF61725E"
	         color2="FF61725E"
	         alternative_color="FF61725E"
	         alternative_color2="FF61725E"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_forest_people_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_forest_people_name}Vanni Forest Tribes"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_forest_people_short_name}Vanni"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_forest_people_text}The tribes known as the Vanni practice slash-and-burn farming in the deep woods, outside the grasp of the Sturgian chiefdoms. They burn down tracts of trees, grow crops on the virgin soil fertilized by ash for a few years until the land is exhausted, and move on. It is an inefficient use of land, but a very efficient use of labor, suitable for a numerically small population in a large area. Also, because the plots are hard to measure and tax, it's a very good strategy for people who don't care to be governed. Indeed, the Vanni are the remnant of the old Vakken people. Long repressed by waves of Sturgian and Nordic migration, they still adhere to the old ways, and are hostile to any who would dare to stop them.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_forest_people_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_forest_people_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_forest_people_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_forest_people_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="eleftheroi"
	         initial_posX="705.0"
	         initial_posY="590.0"
	         banner_key="11.59.59.1500.1500.764.764.1.0.0.108.40.40.582.582.764.615.0.0.0.202.2.2.400.400.865.944.0.0.55.202.2.2.402.423.663.944.0.1.303.340.155.155.266.266.764.496.0.0.0.321.155.155.266.266.760.875.0.0.0.505.155.155.150.43.764.1037.0.0.0.504.155.155.76.32.825.1037.0.0.90.504.155.155.76.32.702.1037.0.1.270"
	         label_color="FFA6825C"
	         color="FFA6825C"
	         color2="FFA6825C"
	         alternative_color="FFA6825C"
	         alternative_color2="FFA6825C"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_eleftheroi_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_eleftheroi_name}Eleftheroi"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_eleftheroi_short_name}Eleftheroi"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_eleftheroi_text}The Eleftheroi, or ‘free people’, live on the steppe lands at the edge of the Calradian Empire. Originally the descendants of runaway slaves and debtors, they soon became highly valued by the local imperial commanders for their knowledge of this frontier zone. Their leaders have been granted titles and their young men taken into the retinues of archons and emperors. But though they are now very loyal to the idea of the Empire, they remain quite hostile to its actual authority, preferring instead to simply patrol the borderlands they call home without interference from anyone.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_eleftheroi_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_eleftheroi_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_eleftheroi_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_eleftheroi_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="guardians"
	         initial_posX="294.0"
	         initial_posY="378.0"
	         banner_key="11.126.126.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.423.148.148.588.621.764.765.0.0.0.504.155.155.360.360.763.700.0.0.0.504.35.35.178.178.763.642.0.0.0.521.155.155.100.100.764.498.0.0.0.449.155.155.261.261.764.879.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color2="FF5A7A4F"
	         alternative_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         alternative_color2="FF5A7A4F"
	         culture="Culture.palaic"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_outlaw_empire_s_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_mafia="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_guardians_name}Rhotian Free Company"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_guardians_short_name}Rhotians"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_guardians_text}The Rhotian Free Company are a unit of auxiliary frontiersmen hailing from the borderlands between the Calradian Empire and Battanian Kingdom. Raised in the region around the city of Rhotae from the Empire's Palaic citizens, they are used to working with the local nobility, specializing in scouting and tracking the often ephemeral traces left by Battanian warbands. But as the Empire descended into civil war, the Rhotians have begun asserting power in the areas in which they live, becoming a law unto themselves and taking what they want from passing imperial caravans. They still will cooperate with imperial authorities, but on their terms and nobody else's.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_guardians_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_guardians_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_guardians_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_guardians_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="chosen_of_the_sky"
	         initial_posX="629.0"
	         initial_posY="515.0"
	         banner_key="34.10.35.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.126.155.155.334.334.764.764.0.0.0.504.155.155.83.139.684.514.0.0.17.504.155.155.83.139.843.516.0.0.-19.504.155.155.83.139.970.607.0.0.-53.504.155.155.83.139.554.602.0.0.51.504.155.155.83.139.498.765.0.0.90.504.155.155.83.139.1023.763.0.1.269.504.155.155.83.139.971.923.0.1.232.504.155.155.83.139.554.927.0.1.128.504.155.155.83.139.842.1014.0.1.198.504.155.155.83.139.683.1016.0.1.162"
	         label_color="FF72583B"
	         color="FF72583B"
	         color2="FF72583B"
	         alternative_color="FF72583B"
	         alternative_color2="FF72583B"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_chosen_of_the_sky_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_sect="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_chosen_of_the_sky_name}Chosen of the Sky"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_chosen_of_the_sky_short_name}Chosen"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_chosen_of_the_sky_text}The Chosen of the Sky are an elite order of warrior priests who worship a divergent sect of nomadic animism. Long spurned by traditional steppe society as heretics, the Chosen have spent the past century wandering the east of Calradia, trading their services to local rulers, and lately to the Calradian Empire, in exchange for supplies and shelter. However, with Calradia plunged into crisis, they have seen an opportunity to enrich themselves, becoming an imposing threat to all in their warpath. Despite their priestly nature, they are not to be underestimated, as the blood of khans past still flows through the veins of their skilled horsemen.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chosen_of_the_sky_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chosen_of_the_sky_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chosen_of_the_sky_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chosen_of_the_sky_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="lochanians"
	         initial_posX="705.0"
	         initial_posY="590.0"
	         banner_key="10.2.126.1536.1536.761.785.1.0.0.407.155.155.494.474.761.745.0.0.0.303.40.40.494.197.766.924.0.0.0.221.40.40.388.388.762.742.0.0.-1"
	         label_color="FF848B65"
	         color="FF848B65"
	         color2="FF848B65"
	         alternative_color="FF848B65"
	         alternative_color2="FF848B65"
	         culture="Culture.byalic"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_lochanians_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_lochanians_name}Sapmelas Forest Tribes"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_lochanians_short_name}Sapmelas"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_lochanians_text}The Sapmelas are the remnants of a tribal people which once occupied the north-eastern extent of the Byalic Sea. Whilst their territory once included vast tracts of forest and tundra, centuries of relentless conflict with the peoples of the Calradian steppe have slowly pushed them southwards from their traditional homeland. The Sapmelas now dwell among the dark lakes, swamps and crags known as the Iltan Portages. An outcast group spurned by almost all of Calradia, including their Byalic cousins, the Sapmelas are forced to fight to ensure the survival of their people.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lochanians_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lochanians_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lochanians_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lochanians_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="hawlans"
	         initial_posX="445.0"
	         initial_posY="55.0"
	         banner_key="33.61.10.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.131.40.40.269.269.764.764.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FFF0F0F0"
	         color="FFF0F0F0"
	         color2="FFF0F0F0"
	         alternative_color="FFF0F0F0"
	         alternative_color2="FFF0F0F0"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_hawlans"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_hawlans_name}Hawlan Rebels"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_hawlans_short_name}Hawlans"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_hawlans_text}The Hawlans are just one of the innumerable nomadic peoples from the steppe lands to the far east of Calradia. Long ago, they were enslaved by the tribes of the Iltanlar, and brought across the wide expanse of the steppes with their migrating overlords. With Calradia in crisis, some Hawlans have found themselves pressed into service in the vast hordes of the Iltanlar, providing a core of expendable footmen badly needed by the mounted nomads. However, this group of rebellious Hawlans have recently broken free, and now fight their former masters for the freedom of their people.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hawlans_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hawlans_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hawlans_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_hawlans_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="seax"
	         initial_posX="530.0"
	         initial_posY="595.0"
	         banner_key="17.12.149.1500.1500.764.764.1.0.0.332.155.155.297.297.764.739.0.0.0.434.40.155.344.384.559.764.0.0.0.434.40.155.344.384.969.764.0.1.0.438.40.155.330.330.764.549.0.1.180"
	         label_color="FF66CCFF"
	         color="FF66CCFF"
	         color2="FF66CCFF"
	         alternative_color="FF66CCFF"
	         alternative_color2="FF66CCFF"
	         culture="Culture.nord"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_seax"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_seax_name}Seax Shipfolk"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_seax_short_name}Seax"
	         tier="3"
	         text="{=si_ar_seax_text}The Seax peoples are recent arrivals in Calradia, so named for the long, sturdy knives they use to cut rope onboard their longships. A generation ago, the Nord chieftain Aeric united the disparate bands of raiders and outcasts living along Calradia’s northern coastline to form a mighty mercenary company, selling their services to the highest bidder. Whether they be sea-raiders that have travelled to Calradia and chosen to settle, or men who have fled the feuding clans of their frozen homeland, the Seax fight with the unified ferocity expected of their brutal raiding culture.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_seax_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_seax_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_seax_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_seax_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="ethawians"
	         initial_posX="445.0"
	         initial_posY="55.0"
	         banner_key="11.125.125.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.428.145.145.588.621.764.765.0.0.0.200.5.5.360.360.750.689.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FFF0F0F0"
	         color="FFF0F0F0"
	         color2="FFF0F0F0"
	         alternative_color="FFF0F0F0"
	         alternative_color2="FFF0F0F0"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_ethawians"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_ethawians_name}Ethawians"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_ethawians_short_name}Ethawians"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_ethawians_text}The Ethawians hail from the verdant tropical lands to the south of the Nahasa desert. A fractious nomadic people, often considered primitive by their northern neighbours among the Banu Asera, they have spent the past centuries engaged in constant inter-tribal warfare. It is said that no Ethawian tribe ever holds total sway over the another - at least, not for long. In the recent past, travellers report the land of the Ethawians has seen great and terrible floods, and so small groups have started making forays into the Nahasa, in search of new lands to settle and new enemies to fight.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ethawians_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ethawians_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ethawians_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ethawians_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="lysians"
	         initial_posX="692.0"
	         initial_posY="217.0"
	         banner_key="11.132.132.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.423.2.2.588.625.764.764.0.0.0.119.142.142.200.200.759.674.0.0.0.325.92.92.250.250.764.834.0.0.0.521.142.142.100.100.764.484.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF965228"
	         color="FF965228"
	         color2="FF4F2212"
	         alternative_color="FF965228"
	         alternative_color2="FF4F2212"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_lysians"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_lysians_name}Lysian Freemen"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_lysians_short_name}Lysians"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_lysians_text}The Lysian people hail from the region south of the Strait of Lysia, from which they draw their name. They are descendants of Kannic colonists, who settled the fertile coastal regions of the western Perassic Sea in the days of the Calradian Republic. Centuries ago, their lands were overrun by the legions of the Calradians, and since then, the Lysians have served the Calradian Empire loyally as guardians of their southern border. But as Calradia has descended into civil war, they have begun asserting power in the areas in which they patrol, becoming a law unto themselves in the nascent Quyazic Empire and taking what they want from the scattered desert villages.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lysians_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lysians_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lysians_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_lysians_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="dryatics"
	         initial_posX="705.0"
	         initial_posY="590.0"
	         banner_key="11.92.92.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.409.155.155.500.500.764.764.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF774f3c"
	         color="FF774f3c"
	         color2="FF774f3c"
	         alternative_color="FF774f3c"
	         alternative_color2="FF774f3c"
	         culture="Culture.palaic"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_dryatics"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_dryatics_name}Dryatic Hillmen"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_dryatics_short_name}Dryatics"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_dryatics_text}The Dryatic Hillmen are one remnant of the ancient Palaic peoples of Calradia, having dwelt in their mountainous homeland in the center of the continent since the days long before the arrival of Calradios the Great. A hardy and resilient people, they have spent countless centuries living in small villages amongst the crags and peaks, droving cattle from the verdant valley floors to the frigid alpine meadows. Whilst technically occupying the lands of the Calradian Empire, unlike many of their Palaic kin they have proved remarkably resistant to Calradicization, retaining most of their language and customs. Their hard lifestyle has made them ideal warriors, prized across Calradia as mercenaries and bodyguards.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_dryatics_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_dryatics_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_dryatics_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_dryatics_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="vezha_valkyries"
	         initial_posX="530.0"
	         initial_posY="595.0"
	         banner_key="33.149.67.1500.1500.764.764.1.0.0.310.40.155.250.250.764.854.0.0.0.112.40.155.297.297.754.704.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF6d62b5"
	         color="FF9382D0"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="FFF4CA14"
	         alternative_color2="FF6d62b5"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_valkyries"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_sect="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_vezha_valkyries_name}Vezha Valkyries"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_vezha_valkyries_short_name}Valkyries"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_vezha_valkyries_text}The Vezha Valkyries are an outcast band of warrior-priestesses from the frigid northern lands of Calradia. Whilst it is not uncommon to see Sturgian and Vakken women fighting to protect their homes and families, the Valkyries believe themselves to be imbued with the spirit of the war-goddess Vezha, taking strict vows to neither marry, nor mother children. Their views fly in the face of traditional northern society, with many viewing the Valkyries as little more than religious extremists. However, nobody can deny their obvious prowess in battle and live to tell the tale, making them highly sought-after as mercenaries in these fraught times.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_vezha_valkyries_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_vezha_valkyries_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_vezha_valkyries_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_vezha_valkyries_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="saleas_sisters"
	         initial_posX="486.0"
	         initial_posY="333.0"
	         banner_key="11.8.8.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.423.7.7.588.625.764.764.0.0.0.308.40.7.350.450.764.764.0.0.45.515.40.7.100.100.764.484.0.0.0.302.40.7.350.480.784.784.0.0.135.341.145.7.183.183.771.606.0.1.90"
	         label_color="FFDB8330"
	         color="FF9E5072"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="FF1F1D1F"
	         alternative_color2="FFc28446"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_saleas_sisters"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_saleas_sisters_name}Sisters of Salea"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_saleas_sisters_short_name}Sisters"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_saleas_sisters_text}The Calradian Empire has always held gladiatorial games involving female fighters, or ‘gladiatrices’, as a curious form of entertainment. However, the Sisters of Salea are a relatively recent revolutionary movement in Calradia's history, being named for the famous champion gladiatrix ‘Salea of Saneopa’, who was brutally strangled to death by her patron after losing a match. Enraged by their colleague's murder, the gladiatrices of Saneopa seized weapons, burned their barracks to the ground and made for the hills, turning to brigandry to survive. Now, the Sisters of Salea are a formidable fighting force, carving a bloody path through anyone in their way.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_saleas_sisters_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_saleas_sisters_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_saleas_sisters_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_saleas_sisters_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="silver_dragon_company"
	         initial_posX="445.0"
	         initial_posY="55.0"
	         banner_key="11.148.148.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.122.19.19.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.500.19.19.618.618.764.764.0.0.0"
	         label_color="0xff6b2929"
	         color="0xff6b2929"
	         color2="0xff7a7a7a"
	         alternative_color="0xff6b2929"
	         alternative_color2="0xff7a7a7a"
	         culture="Culture.rensichou"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_silver_dragon_company"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_silver_dragon_company_name}Company of the Silver Dragon"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_silver_dragon_company_short_name}Silver Dragons"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_silver_dragon_company_text}The Company of the Silver Dragon hails from the lands of a vast and powerful empire, far to the east of Calradia beyond the great steppe. Originally brought to Calradia as mercenaries fighting for the Padishah, little is known about their people in the western lands, save that they produce fine silks and proud warriors. The nomads of the steppe know them as the 'Rensichou', or 'silk-folk', as the steppe is frequently visited by wandering caravans of their silk merchants. However, the Company of the Silver Dragon has gained a well-earned reputation in Calradia as formidable caravan guards, protecting trader far and wide, for a price.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_silver_dragon_company_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_silver_dragon_company_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_silver_dragon_company_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_silver_dragon_company_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="kohi_rohini"
	         initial_posX="445.0"
	         initial_posY="55.0"
	         banner_key="11.7.7.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.427.148.148.500.500.764.864.0.0.0.504.148.148.360.360.764.734.0.0.0.521.148.148.200.200.764.564.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FFD0884E"
	         color="FFD0884E"
	         color2="FFD0884E"
	         alternative_color="FFD0884E"
	         alternative_color2="FFD0884E"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_kohi_rohini"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_kohi_rohini_name}Kohi Rohini Hillmen"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kohi_rohini_short_name}Kohi Rohini"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_kohi_rohini_text}The Kohi Rohini Hillmen are a variety of tribal peoples who take the name of their mountainous homeland, where the desolate lands of the Darshi Marches meet the grasslands of the Calradian Steppe. For centuries, they have eked out a meagre existence on the high mountain slopes, raising flocks of goats amidst rocky crags and sheltered valleys. However, it is in the matter of warfare that the Kohi Rohini are renowned throughout Calradia, having served as the cornerstone of the Padishah’s armies for centuries. Today, with the eastern lands of Calradia fractured in constant conflict, the Kohi Rohini sell their swords to the highest bidder, carving a bloody wake wherever they may be.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_kohi_rohini_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_kohi_rohini_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_kohi_rohini_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_kohi_rohini_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="ircara"
	         initial_posX="195.0"
	         initial_posY="399.0"
	         banner_key="1.2.35.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.144.7.0.400.300.764.764.0.0.0.203.7.0.300.400.764.914.0.0.90.203.7.0.300.400.764.614.0.1.270"
	         label_color="FF61725E"
	         color="0xffffffff"
	         color2="FF61725E"
	         alternative_color="0xffffffff"
	         alternative_color2="FF61725E"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_ircarans"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_ircara_name}Ircaran Woodsmen"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_ircara_short_name}Ircarans"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_ircara_text}The Ircaran Woodsmen - so named for the wildlands they dwell in - are the remnants of an old Vakken realm that once stretched from Lake Laconis to the Cursion Escarpment, on the borders of the Battanian territories. They are the original inhabitants of the northern lands of the continent, having lived in the frigid wastes and dark forests since before the coming of Calradios the Great. However, today the Ircaran Woodsmen are in serious decline, with successive encroachments by both the Sturgians and Calradians reducing their holdings to little more than a scatter of villages along the edge of the woods outside Omor. Despite their apparent frailty, there are few who have met the Ircaran in battle would dare repeat the experience of facing their warriors, whose axe-wielding silhouettes, clad in furs, have gained them a formidable reputation.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ircara_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ircara_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ircara_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_ircara_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="chandions_champions"
	         initial_posX="472.0"
	         initial_posY="372.0"
	         banner_key="11.94.94.4000.4000.768.768.1.0.0.500.7.7.550.550.764.764.0.0.0.308.40.7.350.450.764.764.0.0.45.302.40.7.350.480.784.784.0.0.135.341.40.7.183.183.771.624.0.1.90"
	         label_color="FFDB8330"
	         color="FF9E5072"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="FF1F1D1F"
	         alternative_color2="FFc28446"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_chandions_champions"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_chandions_champions_name}Champions of Chandion"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_chandions_champions_short_name}Champions"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_chandions_champions_text}Gladiatorial combat has always been a part of life for the citizens of the Calradian Empire. Since the days of Calradios the Great, people from far and wide have come to the arenas of the Calradians to either view or participate in the brutal blood sport, which has produced an innumerable list of champions over the centuries. One such champion was the gladiator Chandion, whose rise to the top of the lists in the arena of Zeonica earned him fame across the continent. Since being granted his freedom from the sand, Chandion has formed a small mercenary company out of other gladiators, now fighting not for sport, but for the denars of whoever is willing to pay them.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chandions_champions_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chandions_champions_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chandions_champions_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_chandions_champions_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="druids"
	         initial_posX="261.0"
	         initial_posY="509.0"
	         banner_key="11.40.40.4000.4000.768.768.1.0.0.500.2.7.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.223.2.7.400.400.764.764.0.1.90"
	         label_color="FF848B65"
	         color="0xffffffff"
	         color2="FF848B65"
	         alternative_color="0xffffffff"
	         alternative_color2="FF848B65"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_druids"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_druids_name}Druids of Ailta Druin"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_druids_short_name}Druids"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_druids_text}The Druids of Ailta Druin - so named for the mountainous region in which they dwell - are a religious order that has for centuries served as the religious officials of the Battanian Kingdom. Indeed, for one to become the high king of the Battanians, they must be crowned atop the rock of Dunglanys by the chief shaman of the druidic order. A secretive and mysterious order, the Druids of Ailta Druin are widely regarded across Calradia as heretics, known for sacrificing fair maidens to the spirits of the Otherworld and reading dread portents in the skies. Despite this, a group of druids choose to wander the world, and will serve any willing to have them.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_druids_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_druids_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_druids_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_druids_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="yachios_free_company"
	         initial_posX="445.0"
	         initial_posY="55.0"
	         banner_key="11.67.97.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.309.7.0.250.250.777.764.0.1.225.427.7.0.400.300.644.764.0.1.270.521.7.0.100.100.764.544.0.0.0.427.7.0.400.300.884.764.0.0.90"
	         label_color="0xFF4E3A55"
	         color="0xFF4E3A55"
	         color2="0xffB57A1E"
	         alternative_color="0xFF4E3A55"
	         alternative_color2="0xffB57A1E"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.party_template_yachios_free_company"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_yachios_free_company_name}Yachios Free Company"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_yachios_free_company_short_name}Yachioi"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_yachios_free_company_text}The citizens of the Calradian frontier colony of Yachios have long been prized across the continent for their martial prowess, having tended to the windswept borders of the Nahasa for centuries. Every year, those who have recently reached manhood are assembled in the main square and then allocated to the varying military companies of the colony. One such group is the ‘Yachios Free Company’ - a group of warriors who choose not to serve the colony, but to roam the lands of Calradia and fight as mercenaries. With the recent expansion of the Aserai and subsequent isolation of Yachios from the remainder of the Calradian Empire, this group has gained an additional impetus, and will fight for or against all comers, for the right price.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_yachios_free_company_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_yachios_free_company_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_yachios_free_company_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_yachios_free_company_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="swadians"
	         initial_posX="136.0"
	         initial_posY="504.0"
	         banner_key="11.142.5.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.307.5.142.400.400.764.924.0.0.90.125.5.142.400.400.744.694.0.0.0"
	         label_color="0xff6b2929"
	         color="0xff6b2929"
	         color2="0xffF7BF46"
	         alternative_color="0xff6b2929"
	         alternative_color2="0xffF7BF46"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_swadians_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_swadians_name}Swadian Free Company"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_swadians_short_name}Swadians"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_swadians_text}The Swadian Plains - the verdant lands extending from the Trand River north to the Western Ocean - have long been an integral part of the territory of the Vlandian people. As the focus of the Calradian Empire moved ever eastward, the lands gradually became a rural backwater, their towns declining in importance as many of their most wealthy and influential citizens emigrated to follow the center of imperial power. However, these lands offered incoming Vlandian settlers a promise. Today, the people of the Swadian Plain form a distinct class within Vlandian society, being renowned horsemen and warriors that comprise much of the nascent kingdom’s army. However, some Swadian horsemen prefer to sell their services to the highest bidder, comprising one of Calradia’s most deadly mercenary companies.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_swadians_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_swadians_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_swadians_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_swadians_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="biscan_exiles"
	         initial_posX="136.0"
	         initial_posY="504.0"
	         banner_key="12.145.126.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.101.5.5.450.450.764.764.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color2="FF5A7A4F"
	         alternative_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         alternative_color2="FF5A7A4F"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_biscan_exiles_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_biscan_exiles_name}Biscan Exiles"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_biscan_exiles_name}Biscans"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_biscan_exiles_text}The people of the Biscan Coast have long lived between two worlds. Originally part of the Calradian heartland known for its opulent estates and expansive vineyards, the Biscan Coast was also one of the first places that Vlandian travellers first landed in. Over the centuries, these Vlandians integrated peacefully with the local population, intermarrying with Calradian citizens to form a distinct sub-culture renowned for their martial prowess. Now, with the Vlandians in open rebellion against the Calradian Empire, many Biscans find themselves torn between loyalties, preferring to band together in an exile mercenary company than to openly declare for either side.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_biscan_exiles_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_biscan_exiles_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_biscan_exiles_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_biscan_exiles_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="paravenos_exiles"
	         initial_posX="136.0"
	         initial_posY="504.0"
	         banner_key="3.86.8.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.328.5.5.300.300.624.594.0.0.0.328.5.5.300.300.904.934.0.0.0.100.5.5.250.250.904.614.0.0.0.100.5.5.250.250.624.914.0.0.0"
	         label_color="0xFFBF4972"
	         color="0xFFBF4972"
	         color2="0xffDEA940"
	         alternative_color="0xFFBF4972"
	         alternative_color2="0xffDEA940"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_paravenos_exiles_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_paravenos_exiles_name}Paravenos Exiles"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_paravenos_exiles_name}Paravenoi"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_paravenos_exiles_text}Paravenos - the ancient capital of the Calradian Empire - once shone as a jewel in the crown that was the western provinces. These verdant lands of rolling green hills and lush forests once comprised the heartland of the Calradian people. However, time has not been kind to these lands, with the movement of imperial power eastward, as well as successive waves of invasion and settlement by foreign peoples, reducing the once great cities of the west to little more than shanty towns. Such was the fate of Paravenos. With the foundation of the Vlandian Kingdom, many citizens of Paravenos have found themselves alienated from their lands and forced into exile. Whilst some have taken their exile meekly, some have decided to continue the fight, forming one of the most effective mercenary companies in Calradia.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_paravenos_exiles_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_paravenos_exiles_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_paravenos_exiles_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_paravenos_exiles_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="companions_of_theudaris"
	         initial_posX="136.0"
	         initial_posY="504.0"
	         banner_key="1.73.2.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.307.127.127.400.400.864.764.0.1.0.307.127.127.400.400.664.764.0.0.0.220.127.127.100.100.764.564.0.1.0"
	         label_color="FF5A7A4F"
	         color="FF2D3F1D"
	         color2="FF2D3F1D"
	         alternative_color="FF2D3F1D"
	         alternative_color2="FF2D3F1D"
	         culture="Culture.massa"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_companions_of_theudaris_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         is_nomad="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_companions_of_theudaris_name}Companions of Theudaris"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_companions_of_theudaris_name}Companions"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_companions_of_theudaris_text}Since their inception, the Massa have always been a nomadic people, wandering the lands of western Calradia, living off the land and taking what they want from the defenseless outlying villages. However, in recent years, the Massa have begun to settle somewhat, trading their wandering caravans for high walls, and enslaving villages to produce their food and goods, rather than raiding for them. Theudaris was an exception to this. A chief of a minor noble family among the tribe, he resisted the centralizing influences of his kin, taking his warband into the Epiric Hills to continue their lifestyle of travel and plunder. Upon his death, his movement only gained in traction, and now young warriors from across the Massa flock to the banners that he once flew. Whilst viewed as little more than bandits by their kin, as well as the Calradians and Vlandians that they raid, the Companions of Theudaris now roam the land, raiding indiscriminately, and selling their swords any with the coin to pay them.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_companions_of_theudaris_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_companions_of_theudaris_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_companions_of_theudaris_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_companions_of_theudaris_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="geroianys_free_company"
	         initial_posX="486.0"
	         initial_posY="333.0"
	         banner_key="3.68.12.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.333.5.5.250.250.624.614.0.0.0.333.5.5.250.250.904.914.0.0.0.310.5.5.250.250.904.614.0.0.0.310.5.5.250.250.624.914.0.0.0"
	         label_color="0xFFBF4972"
	         color="0xff9776a9"
	         color2="0xFFAC5F2E"
	         alternative_color="0xff9776a9"
	         alternative_color2="0xFFAC5F2E"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_geroianys_free_company_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_geroianys_free_company_name}Geroianys Free Company"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_geroianys_free_company_name}Geroians"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_geroianys_free_company_text}For centuries, the young men of the colony town of Geroianys, on the island of Perassis Major, were expected to serve for five years in the service of the Calradian imperial navy, whose mighty warships were based in the ports of the island. Over the generations, they won victories against all foes, from the disorganized pirates of the Perassic, to the vast fleets of the Kannic city state of Razih. However, those great wars and their victories were long ago. The Perassic, long subdued by the Calradian Empire, is today little more than a peaceful pond for fishing boats, merchantmen and the bejeweled pleasure craft of the Calradian nobility, and so the imperial navy of old has faded into legend - its ships broken up and its harbors emptied. Without a cause, many in Geroianys now serve in the town’s free company. Though ill-suited for warfare on land, they have nonetheless proved to be effective mercenaries, selling their skills with the spear, axe and bow to the highest bidder.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_geroianys_free_company_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_geroianys_free_company_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_geroianys_free_company_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_geroianys_free_company_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<Faction id="amprela_free_company"
	         initial_posX="705.0"
	         initial_posY="590.0"
	         banner_key="3.67.133.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.90.523.5.5.250.250.624.614.0.0.0.523.5.5.250.250.904.914.0.0.0.126.5.5.250.250.904.614.0.0.0.126.5.5.250.250.624.914.0.0.0"
	         label_color="0xFFBF4972"
	         color="0xffd31dab"
	         color2="0xffEFC990"
	         alternative_color="0xffd31dab"
	         alternative_color2="0xffEFC990"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.kingdom_hero_party_amprela_free_company_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         is_minor_faction="true"
	         is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_amprela_free_company_name}Amprela Free Company"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_amprela_free_company_name}Amprelans"
	         tier="4"
	         text="{=si_ar_amprela_free_company_text}Amprela - the Calradian colony with perhaps the closest connection with the eastern steppe - has one of the most entrenched martial cultures on the continent. Every man, woman and child is expected to pitch in for the defense of the town, from fletching arrows, to filling buckets of water, to fighting in the shield wall. However, there are some young men who decide not to fight for their town, instead electing to serve in the Amprela Free Company. Armed with fine spears and powerful short bows, these mercenaries are highly proficient in combatting the marauding horsemen of the steppe, and so are prized across the continent. Indeed, there are many who claim that a would-be conqueror of the steppe would not get far without the sons of Amprela marching under their banner.">
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_amprela_free_company_leader_0"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_amprela_free_company_leader_1"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_amprela_free_company_leader_2"/>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.AR_spc_amprela_free_company_leader_3"/>
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
	<!--
	Bandits
	-->
	<Faction id="brigands"
	         banner_key="33.125.116.1771.1771.764.764.1.0.0.319.149.116.269.269.760.764.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF8B7C73"
	         color="FF8B7C73"
	         color2="FF8B7C73"
	         alternative_color="FF8B7C73"
	         alternative_color2="FF8B7C73"
	         culture="Culture.looters"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.brigands_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="none"
	         is_bandit="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_brigands_name}Vagabonds"
	         tier="1"/>
	<Faction id="slavers"
	         banner_key="11.101.101.1771.1771.764.764.1.0.0.303.116.116.550.550.764.744.0.0.45.303.116.116.550.550.764.744.0.1.315.342.116.116.224.224.752.914.0.1.0"
	         label_color="FF8B7C73"
	         color="FF8B7C73"
	         color2="FF8B7C73"
	         alternative_color="FF8B7C73"
	         alternative_color2="FF8B7C73"
	         culture="Culture.looters"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.slavers_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="none"
	         is_bandit="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_slavers_name}Slavers"
	         tier="1"/>
	<Faction id="rebel_gladiators"
	         banner_key="11.38.9.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.302.116.116.500.500.764.664.0.0.90.306.116.116.420.500.764.814.0.0.90"
	         label_color="FF8B7C73"
	         color="FF8B7C73"
	         color2="FF8B7C73"
	         alternative_color="FF8B7C73"
	         alternative_color2="FF8B7C73"
	         culture="Culture.looters"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.rebel_gladiators_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="none"
	         is_bandit="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_rebel_gladiators_name}Rebel Gladiators"
	         tier="1"/>
	<!--Faction id="perassic_pirates"
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.307.40.40.500.500.764.764.0.1.315.307.40.40.500.500.764.764.0.0.45.333.40.40.150.150.749.814.0.0.0"
	         label_color="FF8B7C73"
	         color="0xff1a1a1a"
	         color2="0xff1a1a1a"
	         alternative_color="0xff1a1a1a"
	         alternative_color2="0xff1a1a1a"
	         culture="Culture.looters"
	         default_party_template="PartyTemplate.rebel_gladiators_template"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="none"
	         is_bandit="true"
	         is_outlaw="true"
	         name="{=si_ar_perassic_pirates_name}Perassic Pirates"
	         tier="1"/-->
</Factions>