<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Kingdoms>
	<!-- 
	MAJOR KINGDOM FACTIONS
	-->
	<!--
	Aserai Emirates
	-->
	<Kingdom id="aserai"
	         owner="Hero.lord_3_18"
	         banner_key="11.0.0.4345.4345.764.764.1.0.0.463.1.1.466.466.764.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xffB57A1E"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xff4E1A13"
	         label_color="FFebce5e"
	         color="FF965228"
	         color2="FF4F2212"
	         alternative_color="FF1F1D1F"
	         alternative_color2="FFebce5e"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_c"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_a"
	         name="{=aseraifaction}Aserai Emirates"
	         short_name="{=aseraimembers}Aserai"
	         title="{=UsbwPmYb}Aserai Emirates"
	         ruler_title="{=5djtBrHj}Emir"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_aserai_text}The vast Nahasa - the ‘Great Bronze Desert’ - is an unforgiving place of shifting sands, and so too are its people hardy yet changeable. The Calradian Empire always preferred not to send its legions into the army-devouring wastes of the Nahasa. Instead, it projected its power into this borderland by cultivating client rulers among the Aserai clans, who have competed in an endless dance of power since time immemorial. Those clans that could secure a hold on the oases won an imperial subsidy to protect passing caravans and grew rich. Those who could not were pushed into the desert, left to raise goats and raid caravans until they could plot a comeback. In recent centuries, the largest and most powerful of the oasis-dwelling clans have strengthened their authority, forming a series of small emirates that vie for control of the many caravan routes crisscrossing the desert. Whilst these small states may seem to spend the majority of their time fighting amongst themselves, they do sometimes come together to fight a common enemy. This unity, however, is only temporary, and as soon as the foe is defeated, the Aserai return to their traditional infighting. Indeed, it would take someone of incredible strength of character to truly unify the Nahasa under a single banner.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.empire_s"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_the_commons"/>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Battanian Kingdom
	-->
	<Kingdom id="battania"
	         owner="Hero.lord_5_3"
	         banner_key="11.2.2.6296.6296.764.764.1.0.0.460.3.3.457.457.764.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff284E19"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffB4F0F1"
	         label_color="FF55831A"
	         color="FF2D3F1D"
	         color2="FFBFCBB0"
	         alternative_color="FFD69516"
	         alternative_color2="FF55831A"
	         culture="Culture.battania"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_e"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=0B27RrYJ}Battanian Kingdom"
	         short_name="{=bgjiFSHZ}Battanians"
	         title="{=qaDIU0XC}High Kingdom of the Battanians"
	         ruler_title="{=afvM7XpQ}High King"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_battania_text}From time immemorial there has been a high king of Battania, crowned with great ceremony on the sacred hill of Dunthanach to reign over the dark, mysterious forests and stony crags of the Uchalion Plateau. Ask any Battanian chieftain, however, whose ‘kingdom’ he lives in, and he will look around at his hall and his fields and his pastures, his flocks and his retainers, and answer ‘Mine, of course!’ The Battanians are, by nature, a free spirited and fiercely independent people, though they prove to be single-mindedly determined in both protecting what is theirs, and taking what is others. Only lately, following the example of the Calradian Empire, have the high kings of Battania made any effort to exert their authority. ‘Such unruly cattle as my people require a strong herdsman's hand to steer them from the ravine and protect them from the wolf,’ said one recent high king, just before he was betrayed by a jealous cousin and taken in chains to the nearest imperial outpost.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.massa"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_cantons"/>
			<policy id="policy_lawspeakers"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Calradian Empire
	-->
	<Kingdom id="empire_s"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_1_8"
	         banner_key="11.6.6.4345.4345.768.768.1.0.0.162.7.7.512.512.769.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff382188"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffDEA940"
	         label_color="FF6d62b5"
	         color="FF9382D0"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="FFF4CA14"
	         alternative_color2="FF6d62b5"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_s_name}Calradian Empire"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_s_short_name}Calradian Empire"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_s_title}Calradian Empire"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_s_ruler_title}Emperor"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_s_text}According to tradition, the first Calradians entered the continent as exiles, following Calradios the Great across the vast Western Ocean to found the great city of Charasea. Over time, the Calradians relentlessly expanded their territories across the continent, founding new colonies and conquering neighboring peoples until soon, their empire stretched from the Western Ocean to the Great Eastern Steppe. Cunning politics ensured new peoples and cultures were assimilated into the Empire, whilst the might of the legions ensured the stability of the borders. However, recently cracks have started to form in the very heart of the Calradian Empire, pitting brother against brother in a series of devastating civil wars. Smelling weakness, barbarians now make frequent incursions into the imperial borderlands to raid, or worse, to carve out their own kingdoms. Despite this, to many in the Calradian heartland, life continues much as it always has. Farmers still toil under a blazing sun, the Calradian Senate still meets to debate matters of state, and the vaunted imperial legions have lost none of their potency, carrying the Dragon Banner of Calradios forward to victory.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.empire"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="true"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_royal_privilege"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Eastern Calradian Despotate
	-->
	<Kingdom id="empire"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_1_5"
	         banner_key="11.4.4.4345.4345.768.768.1.0.0.163.5.5.512.512.769.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff793191"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
	         label_color="FF850C6D"
	         color="FF4E3A55"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="FFffffff"
	         alternative_color2="FF660653"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_n_name}Eastern Calradian Despotate"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_n_short_name}Eastern Calradian Despotate"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_n_title}Eastern Calradian Despotate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_n_ruler_title}Emperor"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_n_text}For the last two centuries, the vaunted legions of the Calradian Empire have won fame and fortune in the east, expanding the frontier greatly into the former lands of the Palaic people who dwelt beyond the Dryatic Mountains. Halted when they reached the shores of Lake Tanaesis, they drained marshes and turned the river floodplains into wheatfields, cut back forests and turned the hillsides into pasture. However, the shifting fortunes of life on the eastern frontier have turned over the past centuries, and thundering hooves can be heard far and wide across the steppes of the east. In 949, this came to a head when, forced onwards by nomadic incursions, the Byalic people invaded the Calradian Empire, killing Emperor Themestios Comnos in battle and routing his armies. The situation was restored by the talented - albeit decidedly insane - general Zenon of the Neretzes family, who succeeded in defeating the Byals, halting their advance further into imperial territory and reclaiming the Dragon Banner of Calradios. Though he sent the banner back to imperial authorities as a gesture of goodwill, his troops hailed him as emperor, splitting the Calradian Empire and igniting the civil war that now rages. Zenon, now styling himself Solarios 'Light-Giver', has since forged the eastern provinces into a powerful empire, driving the armies of friend and foe alike before his battle-hardened legions.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.empire_s"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="true"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_sacred_majesty"/>
			<policy id="policy_feudal_inheritance"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Western Calradian Republic
	-->
	<Kingdom id="empire_w"
	         owner="Hero.lord_NE9_l"
	         banner_key="11.8.8.4345.4345.768.768.1.0.0.164.9.9.512.512.769.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff591645"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffFFAD54"
	         label_color="FFDB8330"
	         color="FF9E5072"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="FF1F1D1F"
	         alternative_color2="FFc28446"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_a"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_w_name}Western Calradian Republic"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_w_short_name}Western Calradian Republic"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_w_title}Western Calradian Republic"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_w_ruler_title}Emperor"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_empire_w_text}The western lands of Calradia form the spiritual heartland of the Calradian people. It was this land which, over a millennium ago, saw the arrival of Calradios the Great and his companions on the coast of the continent, founding the colony of Charasea and laying the foundation of an empire which would last through the ages. But the Calradian Empire’s center of gravity has since moved further eastwards, and their original heartland - has been lost to both the Vlandians and Massa. The west of the Empire today, a warm green land of oak forests and volcanic outcrops, was mostly conquered from the Palaic tribes. Over the centuries, they have intermarried with Calradian colonists and today their old languages and customs are mostly forgotten. Service in the legions has traditionally been a path out of rural poverty and many an ambitious general has drawn his most loyal recruits from this region. Facing an existential threat to their ancestral lands and way of life, the senators of the western provinces voted for secession from the Empire, hailing the Archon of Charasea as Emperor to lead them and raising legions to fight both friend and foe.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.vlandia"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_land_grants_for_veterans"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Iltanlar Khanate
	-->
	<Kingdom id="khuzait"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_6_1"
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4345.4345.780.802.1.0.0.128.11.0.200.200.764.759.0.0.0.401.11.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.500.11.0.353.353.764.764.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff1a1a1a"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffEFC990"
	         label_color="FF7CC8EB"
	         color="0xff1a1a1a"
	         color2="FFCCBB89"
	         alternative_color="0xff1a1a1a"
	         alternative_color2="FF6caecc"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_iltanlar_name}Iltanlar Khanate"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_iltanlar_short_name}Iltanlar"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_iltanlar_title}Iltanlar Khanate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_iltanlar_ruler_title}Khan"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_iltanlar_text}According to myth, the myriad of nomadic peoples who dwell in the vast steppe east of Calradia are the descendants of the ten sons of the great she-wolf, who taught her sons how to tame horses and hunt in packs like the wolves. One such son was Iltan - the ‘mountain wolf’ - who was destined to climb the highest peaks and howl in mockery at those who dwelled on the plains below. His scions - the Iltanlar - have carried on this legacy, rejecting their plains-dwelling nomadic kin and instead settling in the highland tundra of the Sulun Dag Mountains. For centuries, they were content in their mountain home, venturing into the western lands only to raid and trade, and then returning to their ancestral freedom. However, even the most adventurous rider eventually becomes weary, and the Iltanlar gradually confederated and came to settle on the western plateau known as the Devseg, earning their Calradicized name due to their frequent travels into the Iltan Portages. Whilst each tribe still retains its autonomy, it is the law of the steppe that the strongest shall rule and the weakest shall serve, and so the Iltanlar have formed an uneasy tribal alliance, hailing their leader as Khan. Now, with the Calradian Empire in crisis, the Iltanlar look outwards, their eyes ever searching for riches to plunder and lands to take for their own.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.tanash"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_grazing_rights"/>
			<policy id="policy_sacred_majesty"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Sturgian Chiefdoms
	-->
	<Kingdom id="sturgia"
	         owner="Hero.lord_2_1"
	         banner_key="11.12.12.4345.4345.768.768.1.0.0.462.13.13.512.512.769.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff224277"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffCEDAE7"
	         label_color="FF1856A1"
	         color="FF1C2A50"
	         color2="FF949CCC"
	         alternative_color="FFFFFFFF"
	         alternative_color2="FF2A4B78"
	         culture="Culture.sturgia"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_b"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_c"
	         name="{=PjO7oY16}Sturgian Chiefdoms"
	         short_name="{=C4qjBqLO}Sturgians"
	         title="{=iYCR3xuQ}Sturgian Chiefdoms"
	         ruler_title="{=FmbgPGBL}Boyar"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_sturgia_text}The people who dwell in the frigid north of Calradia - collectively referred to as the Sturgians - have long been ruled over by a collection of petty chiefs and kings, each maintaining their small holdings at the edges of the dark forests and along the icy coastlines. As boomtowns sprung up alongside the bays and lakes of the north, the local tribal leaders forged marriage pacts with Nords and other adventurers, trading amber and furs for their swords to expand their realms by subduing their neighboring Sturgian or Vakken groups. However, despite their shared ancestry, the Sturgians refuse to unify under a single banner, even refusing to use the term 'king'. Instead, the petty chiefs of Sturgia occasionally come together to follow the strongest warrior during times of crisis, forming a loose confederation with shared goals. In recent decades, however, the leader of the powerful Gundaroving chiefdom - a particularly warlike Nordic lineage - has sought to increase their power over the other chiefs, convincing them through cunning politics and shows of force that the best option for the Sturgians is to come together and conquer. Now, the Sturgian Chiefdoms look outwards, seeking to unify the entire north under their rule.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.vaegiria"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_lawspeakers"/>
			<policy id="policy_precarial_land_tenure"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Vlandian Kingdom
	-->
	<Kingdom id="vlandia"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_4_1"
	         banner_key="11.14.14.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.160.15.15.512.512.769.764.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff6b2929"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffF7BF46"
	         label_color="ffB01301"
	         color="0xff6b2929"
	         color2="FFECBA44"
	         alternative_color="0xff6b2929"
	         alternative_color2="ff910101"
	         culture="Culture.vlandia"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_d"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_c"
	         name="{=FjwRsf1C}Vlandian Kingdom"
	         short_name="{=8HMyTKF6}Vlandians"
	         title="{=lAWwcO6b}Kingdom of Vlandia"
	         ruler_title="{=hwnp9abW}King"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_vlandia_text}The people today known as the Vlandians are said to have come to Calradia from overseas. Mercenaries and adventurers who spoke the tongues of many lands, they took their name from one of their first warlords - Wilund the Bold - known as ‘Valandion’ in Calradic. Their heavy cavalry, second to none, ran down the foes of the Calradian Empire from the shifting southern sands to the distant eastern steppe. But the Calradian Empire has never had as much coin as it needed, and so treasury officials soon learned that it could pay its auxiliary troops just as well with land grants and titles. This was perhaps not the most far-sighted of policies, however. When not riding under the Dragon Banner, the Vlandians were settled in the western lands of the Calradian Empire, where they married, planted farms, and built towns and fortresses of their own. It was not difficult, during the recent interregnum, for Osric 'Iron-Arm' to declare himself king - independent in all but name. He in turn has recognized his lieutenants as barons and counts, granting them suzerainty over their lands in exchange for rallying to his banner in war. Now, the young kingdom looks greedily outwards, eyeing the rich and defenseless lands of the Calradian Empire for further conquest.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.empire_w"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_feudal_inheritance"/>
			<policy id="policy_castle_charters"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Spahanfar Satrapy
	-->
	<Kingdom id="spahad"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_12_1"
	         banner_key="11.101.0.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.502.1.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.411.1.0.120.120.764.764.0.0.0.506.1.0.200.200.864.864.0.0.45.506.1.0.200.200.864.664.0.0.-45.506.1.0.200.200.664.864.0.0.-45.506.1.0.200.200.664.664.0.0.45.503.1.0.50.50.764.764.0.0.90.503.1.0.50.50.764.664.0.0.90.503.1.0.50.50.764.864.0.0.90.503.1.0.50.50.864.764.0.0.90.503.1.0.50.50.664.764.0.0.90.500.1.0.75.75.764.764.0.0.90"
	         primary_banner_color="0xFFAC5F2E"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xff591645"
	         label_color="FFebce5e"
	         color="0xFFAC5F2E"
	         color2="0xff591645"
	         alternative_color="0xFFAC5F2E"
	         alternative_color2="0xff591645"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_c"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_a"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_spahad_name}Spahanfar Satrapy"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_spahad_short_name}Spahanfari"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_spahad_title}Spahanfar Satrapy"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_spahad_ruler_title}Shah"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_spahad_text}For millennia, the vast tracts of desert and steppe to the east of Calradia have been occupied by a myriad of Darshi-speaking peoples, each ruled over by petty shahs or khans. At some point many centuries ago, many of these groups united to form the Darshi Empire, with the most powerful ruler among them taking on the title of ‘Padishah’. Since then, many scholars have taken to calling the Darshi the ‘Calradia of the East’. Indeed, the two empires have often clashed with each other over both the deserts of the Nahasa and the steppes of the east. Whilst seeming monolithic in nature, many of the old Darshi realms remain as satrapies under the Darshi Empire, with their petty shahs still allowed some autonomy to govern their own affairs. The Spahanfar are one of these satraps, dwelling on the furthest western imperial borderlands, where they meet the lands of Calradia. Over the years, they have made frequent incursions into the Devseg and Nahasa, often alongside the reigning padishahs, gaining significant land, wealth and prestige in the process. However, with chaos engulfing the Calradian Empire, and the nomads of the deserts and steppe coalescing into substantial realms, it remains to be seen if the Darshi may continue their expansion, or be forced to go on the defensive.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.aserai"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_sacred_majesty"/>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!-- 
	LESSER KINGDOM FACTIONS
	-->
	<!--
	Alkit Khanate
	-->
	<Kingdom id="alkit"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_10_1"
	         banner_key="11.25.10.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.427.11.11.400.400.764.923.1.0.0.129.11.11.300.300.759.694.1.0.0.340.11.11.200.200.764.484.1.0.0.504.11.11.90.90.718.476.1.0.-40.504.11.11.90.90.810.477.1.0.39.410.11.11.113.113.764.879.1.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff7a7a7a"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffFFAD54"
	         label_color="FF7CC8EB"
	         color="0xff7a7a7a"
	         color2="0xffFFAD54"
	         alternative_color="0xff7a7a7a"
	         alternative_color2="0xffFFAD54"
	         culture="Culture.khuzait"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_alkit_name}Alkit Khanate"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_alkit_short_name}Alkit"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_alkit_title}Alkit Khanate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_alkit_ruler_title}Khan"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_alkit_text}The past century of Calradian history has seen the rise of many short-lived kingdoms, each attempting to gain land and power from the instability of the Calradian Empire. The Alkit Khanate is one such state. Two generations ago, the Calradian Emperor Zaricos Comnos hired tribes of the Iltanlar to retake the colony of Varnapolys from Nordic invaders. The Alkit eagerly accepted the imperial contract, drawing on the wanderlust of other nomadic tribes to form a vast host and soon defeating the outnumbered Nords. Rewarded with stewardship of Varnapolys in the Empire's name, the Alkit found themselves among the most powerful peoples on the continent. However, the steppe breeds an unquenchable restlessness, and so the Alkit soon betrayed the Empire, cutting a swathe of conquest through the divided Sturgian and Vakken realms to form their own realm from the ashes. Now, the Alkit Khanate is on the defensive, unable to gain support from the other Iltanlar clans of their homeland far to the east, and so must fight for survival of their new realm.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.sturgia"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_sacred_majesty"/>
			<policy id="policy_lawspeakers"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Byalic Confederation
	-->
	<Kingdom id="byals"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_13_1"
	         banner_key="11.7.7.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.421.12.12.500.500.764.744.0.0.90.433.12.12.150.150.764.769.0.1.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xffF7BF46"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xff224277"
	         label_color="FFebce5e"
	         color="0xffF7BF46"
	         color2="0xff224277"
	         alternative_color="0xffF7BF46"
	         alternative_color2="0xff224277"
	         culture="Culture.byalic"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_e"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_byals_name}Byalic Confederation"
	         short_name="{si_ar_kingdom_byals_short_name}Byals"
	         title="{si_ar_kingdom_byals_title}Byalic Confederation"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_byals_ruler_title}High Chieftain"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_jokbyalic_text}To the north of the Calradian steppe dwell a myriad of tribes, referred to by the merchants of the Calradian Empire as the Byals. A hardy people, distantly related the Vakken and tempered by generations of intermarriage with Nord warriors, they have for centuries dwelled in small, isolated villages, carving out a meagre existence raising cattle in sheltered grasslands between the Karakaz River and northern forests, and fishing the frigid waters of the Byalic Sea. However, matters would change in the year 945, when the Nachaghan tribe from the east thundered into Byalic territory, ravging the land and pillaging its settlements. Whilst the Byals mounted a stalwart defense, the sheer numbers of the nomads would prove too much. Threatened with annihilation, many Byals migrated to the south and west, carving a desperate, bloody swathe across the Iltan Portages into the Calradian Empire. They would earn infamy in routing the imperial armies, killing the Emperor Themestios Comnos and causing the civil war that has brought the Calradian Empire to its knees. They now find themselves with small conquests on the Calradian borderlands, far from their home, with bitter enemies on all sides. It remains to be seen how long the Byals may hold out against such seemingly impossible odds.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.empire"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_cantons"/>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Massa Confederation
	-->
	<Kingdom id="massa"
	         owner="Hero.lord_4_5"
	         banner_key="11.12.12.1536.1536.768.768.1.0.0.105.40.127.500.500.764.724.0.0.0.301.40.127.500.500.764.964.0.0.-90"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff429081"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffF7BF46"
	         label_color="ffB01301"
	         color="FF58888B"
	         color2="FFECBA44"
	         alternative_color="FF58888B"
	         alternative_color2="ff910101"
	         culture="Culture.massa"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_d"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_c"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_massa_name}Massa Confederation"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_massa_short_name}Massa"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_massa_title}Confederation of the Massa"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_massa_ruler_title}High Chieftain"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_massa_text}The origins of the people known as the Massa are shrouded in mystery. Some say they came across the Western Ocean, others that they are Nords. Some believe that they are in fact the spirits of the dead, reanimated in the setting sun and sent to plague the earth. What is known, is that the Massa are an aggressive migratory confederation of tribes that appeared on the western shores of Calradia only a few centuries ago. They wilfully ignore imperial laws of land tenure and property ownership, rustling livestock and droving them where they please, whilst their warbands strike against helpless outlying villages, looting and pillaging, before melting back into the woods and hills. Resistant to Calradian control, unlike their Vlandian cousins, the Massa nonetheless found themselves corralled by Calradian forces, with fortifications constructed along their droving routes and garrisons posted to guard imperial villages. Their wanderlust uncontainable, some Massa instead became mercenaries, fighting in the Rhennod Hills with the Battanians, whilst others banded together in a common purpose. Instead of simply plundering villages for their resources, before moving on, the Massa began to settle, enslaving locals to support their warbands for as long as they stayed. This method, though highly destructive, has proven effective in advancing the Massa as true contenders with the great powers. It is unsurprising that the Massa were quick to seize upon recent Calradian weakness, carving a small realm for themselves in the fertile west and ever searching for new lands to conquer and exploit.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.battania"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_castle_charters"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Quyazic Empire
	-->
	<Kingdom id="quyaz"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_9_1"
	         banner_key="11.72.72.4922.4922.776.777.1.0.0.333.5.0.300.300.749.729.0.0.0.423.5.0.507.507.764.751.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff0c4b63"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
	         label_color="FF1856A1"
	         color="0xff0c4b63"
	         color2="FFDE9953"
	         alternative_color="0xff0c4b63"
	         alternative_color2="FFDE9953"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_b"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_c"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_quyaz_name}Quyazic Empire"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_quyaz_short_name}Quyazics"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_quyaz_title}Quyazic Empire"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_quyaz_ruler_title}Basileos"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_quyaz_text}The Kannic colonies of Quyaz once held a vast empire on the southern coasts of the Perassic Sea, renowned for its wealth and power gained through maritime trade and conquest. A series of bloody wars against the Calradian Republic centuries ago resulted in the loss of their freedom to the growing empire, and much much of their culture and language was lost to ‘calradicization’. However, over the last two centuries, raids on the Nahasan borders by the increasingly organized Aserai stretched the southern Calradian garrisons to breaking point, resulting in a number of border castles being overrun. Ineffective imperial administration ignored the pleas of the Quyazic people to protect them, and so the province soon looked to its own protection, raising legions and electing generals from among the local nobility. In the year 941, this would reach a peak when the archon Lamenon Naumatos seized the opportunity and declared independence from the Calradian Empire, founding his own ‘Quyazic Empire’. Whilst Calradian Emperor Themestios Comnos, preoccupied with an endless series of domestic crises, recognized the nascent realm and granted it notional sovereignty, with his death, the Quyazic people now find themselves fighting to defend what is theirs against both the rising Aserai Emirates, as well as their former Calradian overlords.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.aserai"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_land_grants_for_veterans"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Tanash City States
	-->
	<Kingdom id="tanash"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_14_1"
	         banner_key="11.61.154.4345.4345.776.777.1.0.0.404.38.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.117.38.0.250.250.764.764.0.0.0.500.38.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0.521.38.0.150.150.764.534.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff8d5c44"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffF7BF46"
	         label_color="FFebce5e"
	         color="0xff8d5c44"
	         color2="0xffF7BF46"
	         alternative_color="0xff8d5c44"
	         alternative_color2="0xffF7BF46"
	         culture="Culture.darshi"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_c"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_a"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_tanash_name}Tanash City States"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_tanash_short_name}Tanashi"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_tanash_title}Tanash City States"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_tanash_ruler_title}Shah"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_tanash_text}The lands to the east of the vast Lake Tanaesis - known as ‘Tanash’ in the Darshi language - have long been the home of a number of great city states, their inhabitants growing monstrously rich on the trade of silk and spices from the far eastern lands into Calradia. Traditionally a militarily poor people, both the Calradian and Darshi empires have periodically exacted tribute from the Tanashi in return for assuring their sovereignty. However, two generations ago, a Calradian general marched his army across the Iltan Portages and subjugated the Tanash city states in a swift campaign, forming the imperial protectorate of Transtanaesia. Since that time, the Tanashi have chafed under the rule of the Calradians, who have levied ever higher taxes on the people of the region to fund their many wars. Whilst once their cities were bustling centers of commerce, drawing travellers from far and wide, now only dust gathers in many of their taverns and marketplaces. With the winds of change once again blowing, the Tanashi see the impending Calradian civil war as an opportunity to regain their independence, and so have broken free from imperial authority, electing a shah to represent their collective interests in the darkening world.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.khuzait"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Vaegir Kingdom
	-->
	<Kingdom id="vaegiria"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_8_1"
	         banner_key="11.33.33.4000.4000.776.778.1.0.0.306.148.148.312.479.770.930.0.1.-90.503.148.148.124.126.765.619.0.1.90.144.148.148.441.407.773.803.0.1.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xffffffff"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xff4E1A13"
	         label_color="FF1856A1"
	         color="0xffffffff"
	         color2="0xff4E1A13"
	         alternative_color="0xffffffff"
	         alternative_color2="0xff4E1A13"
	         culture="Culture.vakken"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_b"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_c"
	         name="{=si_ar_kingdom_vaegiria_name}Vaegir Kingdom"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_kingdom_vaegiria_short_name}Vaegirs"
	         title="{=si_ar_kingdom_vaegiria_title}Kingdom of the Vaegirs"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_kingdom_vaegiria_ruler_title}King"
	         text="{=si_ar_kingdom_vaegiria_text}For centuries, the term ‘Vaegir’ - meaning ‘northern mercenary’ in Calradic - has been applied by the rulers of the Calradian Empire to a disparate assortment of warriors hailing from the frigid northern lands who have taken contracts to fight in imperial service. The Vaegir Kingdom, however, has only appeared relatively recently, forming from a coalition of Vakken-speaking tribes who fled from the marauding Alkit and other nomads, migrating into the Calradian borderlands of the Ircara Wildlands and joining their kin who dwelt in those lands since time immemorial. A hardy, warlike people with a strict code of honor, the Calradians were quick to see their potential, contracting them to protect the northern border in exchange for sovereignty over the dark forests and frigid tundra. These new Vaegirs were eager to accept Calradian gold and lands, as well as the certainty and security that comes with imperial rule, growing wealthy and powerful by raiding their neighboring Sturgian principalities. With the Calradian Empire falling into civil war, the Vaegirs have found themselves cast adrift, with only their strength and guile standing between success and total destruction.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.sturgia"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_feudal_inheritance"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!-- 
	MINOR KINGDOM FACTIONS
	-->
	<!--
	Amprela Archontate
	-->
	<Kingdom id="amprela"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_18_1"
	         banner_key="11.133.133.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.90.126.5.5.300.300.764.744.0.0.0.423.5.5.500.500.764.764.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xffdf84dc"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffF7BF46"
	         label_color="FF1856A1"
	         color="0xffdf84dc"
	         color2="0xffF7BF46"
	         alternative_color="0xffdf84dc"
	         alternative_color2="0xffF7BF46"
	         culture="Culture.empire_n"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_amprela_faction_name}Amprela Archontate"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_amprela_faction_short_name}Amprelans"
	         title="{=si_ar_amprela_faction_title}Amprela Archontate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_amprela_faction_ruler_title}Archon"
	         text="{=si_ar_amprela_faction_text}{=si_ar_amprela_faction_text}The proud city of Amprela has long stood as the easternmost border of the Calradian Empire, marking the land where the rule of the people of Calradios ends, and the rule of the petty khans and shahs of the east begins. Founded as little more than a military fortress, it has stood throughout the history of the continent as a bulwark, seeing the arrival of countless new peoples from across the sea and steppe. A martial people, many of whom are the descendants of veterans of the original Calradian legions who swept through the land, the citizens of Amprela are a uniquely close-knit collective, with men and women, old and young alike, pitching in to defend the city in times of conflict. The city is also home to the wild Eleftheroi horsemen, whose long-standing service to the Calradian Empire has checked the expansionist goals of khans and shahs many times over the generations. Such features have made Amprela the location from which emperors have based their campaigns further east, though few such endeavors have ever found much in the way of success. Thus was the fate of Emperor Themestios Comnos, whose ill-fated expedition into the Iltan Portages met with disaster only a couple of days' ride from the city walls. Now, with the Calradian Empire descending into civil war, the people of Amprela have once again looked to their own defenses, defying all claimants and declaring themselves for nobody except themselves. A bold strategy indeed, it remains to be seen if Amprela may hold on to its new-found freedoms.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.khuzait"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_the_commons"/>
			<policy id="policy_land_grants_for_veterans"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Geroian Republic
	-->
	<Kingdom id="geroianys"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_17_1"
	         banner_key="11.72.72.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.344.5.0.300.300.764.764.0.0.0.502.5.0.400.400.764.764.0.0.45.518.5.0.150.150.764.549.0.0.90"
	         primary_banner_color="0xff9776a9"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffFFAD54"
	         label_color="FF1856A1"
	         color="0xff9776a9"
	         color2="0xffFFAD54"
	         alternative_color="0xff9776a9"
	         alternative_color2="0xffFFAD54"
	         culture="Culture.kannic"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_geroianys_faction_name}Geroian Republic"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_geroianys_faction_short_name}Geroians"
	         title="{=si_ar_geroianys_faction_title}Geroian Archontate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_geroianys_faction_ruler_title}Archon"
	         text="{=si_ar_geroianys_faction_text}For even the most inexperienced geographer, the Perassic Sea is difficult to miss. This vast sea, bordered by the woods and plains of the Calradian heartland to the north, and the shifting sands of the Nahasa to the south, has seen the rise and fall of countless civilizations, empires, and petty realms. At the center of the Perassic lies two great islands, known as Perassos Megalos and Perassos Mikros in the language of the Calradians, though they go by many other names to the numerous peoples who have charted them. The earliest inhabitants of these islands were Kannic colonists from the city state of Razih, who settled the coasts of the island they called ‘Geroia’ and turned the inland forests to the purpose of ship building, amassing great fleets of merchantmen and warships. However, theirs was to be a story of decline, first conquered by the Calradians at the end of the Quyazic Wars, then stripped of their navy as the Calradians gained dominance over the entire Perassic, turning it into effectively a Calradian-controlled lake. Today, the Perassic is viewed as a sleepy backwater, the Geroian towns and villages little more than shanty towns, and their castles neglected and crumbling. However, the lords of Geroia have waited long for the day when they can rise up and seize power for themselves, and the civil war that has now engulfed the Calradian Empire has provided such an opportunity.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.aserai"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
			<policy id="policy_land_grants_for_veterans"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Paravenos Archontate
	-->
	<Kingdom id="paravenos"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_16_1"
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.521.11.0.100.100.764.564.0.0.0.328.11.0.300.350.764.764.0.1.0.423.11.0.550.550.764.764.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xFFBF4972"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffDEA940"
	         label_color="FF6d62b5"
	         color="0xFFBF4972"
	         color2="0xffDEA940"
	         alternative_color="0xFFBF4972"
	         alternative_color2="0xffDEA940"
	         culture="Culture.empire_w"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_paravenos_faction_name}Paravenos Archontate"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_paravenos_faction_short_name}Paravenoi"
	         title="{=si_ar_paravenos_faction_title}Paravenos Archontate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_paravenos_faction_ruler_title}Archon"
	         text="{=si_ar_paravenos_faction_text}The proud and mighty city of Paravenos was the first major inland colony founded by the Calradians in the days of Calradios the Great. Over the centuries, its opulent halls have played host to the kings, senators and emperors of the various periods of Calradian history, being viewed as one of the most prominent cities of the continent. This position of primacy proved most advantageous to the citizens of Paravenos, their markets filled with merchants from all corners of Calradia, whilst their walls grew taller and their houses ever more lavish. However, cities - like men - grow old, and now Paravenos finds itself a forgotten backwater - the center of political power in the Calradian Empire having followed the campaigning emperors ever further to the east. Today, the archon of the city holds together a fragile realm, with their former servants among the Vlandians and Massa now in open rebellion against imperial authority, surrounding the city in a loose siege. Seeing the imperial authorities at Charasea, Zeonica or Saneopa are preoccupied with their own civil war, the people of Paravenos have taken drastic measures, hailing their archon as emperor and declaring secession, hoping a centralized authority in the city may save it from destruction. Now, Paravenos stands alone, and it remains to be seen how long the ancient capital may survive in this new, shattered world.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.vlandia"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_cantons"/>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Yachios Archontate
	-->
	<Kingdom id="yachios"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_15_1"
	         banner_key="11.116.116.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.119.11.0.300.300.764.764.0.1.15.202.11.0.400.300.624.784.0.1.270.202.11.0.400.300.904.784.0.0.90.500.11.0.600.600.764.771.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xFF4E3A55"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffB57A1E"
	         label_color="FF6d62b5"
	         color="0xFF4E3A55"
	         color2="0xffB57A1E"
	         alternative_color="0xFF4E3A55"
	         alternative_color2="0xffB57A1E"
	         culture="Culture.empire"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_yachios_faction_name}Yachios Archontate"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_yachios_faction_short_name}Yachioi"
	         title="{=si_ar_yachios_faction_short_title}Yachios Archontate"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_yachios_faction_ruler_title}Archon"
	         text="{=si_ar_yachios_faction_text}For centuries, the Calradian Empire has been the dominant power in the Nahasa, exerting its influence over the disparate nomadic tribes of the Banu Asera through both conquest and diplomacy. Part of this strategy has been the foundation of a series of castles and fortified colonies, settling both legionaries and veterans throughout the shifting sands to keep law and order. The colony-town of Yachios is one such outpost, founded during the reign of Emperor Mavinon. It has since been ruled over by the Carasios family, who have fostered strong trade partnerships with the nomadic Aserai and expanded the colony into a true imperial town. However, the politics of Calradia appear to shift as frequently as the sands of the Nahasa, and now change is afoot. The Aserai - once a collection of divided tribes - have now consolidated into a series of powerful emirates, whilst the Calradian legions have almost completely withdrawn from the southern desert. As a result, the people of Yachios now look to themselves for leadership and protection, with some even hailing their archon as emperor. Their realm may be small, but few can deny that generations of time spent in the unforgiving Nahasa have made them hardy and resilient - perhaps enough to survive this changing world.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.aserai"
			              value="1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_senate"/>
			<policy id="policy_land_grants_for_veterans"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
	<!--
	Tahyai Emirates
	-->
	<Kingdom id="tahyai"
	         owner="Hero.AR_lord_15_1"
	         banner_key="11.5.5.4000.4000.764.764.1.0.0.154.91.0.400.400.764.764.0.1.0.500.91.0.500.500.764.764.0.0.0.427.91.0.400.450.764.809.0.0.0"
	         primary_banner_color="0xffFCDE90"
	         secondary_banner_color="0xffa34500"
	         label_color="FF6d62b5"
	         color="0xffFCDE90"
	         color2="0xffa34500"
	         alternative_color="0xffFCDE90"
	         alternative_color2="0xffa34500"
	         culture="Culture.aserai"
	         settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_a"
	         flag_mesh="info_screen_flags_b"
	         name="{=si_ar_tahyai_faction_name}Tahyai Emirates"
	         short_name="{=si_ar_tahyai_faction_short_name}Tahyai"
	         title="{=si_ar_tahyai_faction_short_title}Tahyai Emirates"
	         ruler_title="{=si_ar_tahyai_faction_ruler_title}Emir"
	         text="{=si_ar_tahyai_faction_text}Among the clans of the Nahasa - the ‘Great Bronze Desert’ - there is a dance as unforgiving as the shifting sands. Away from the high walls and bustling streets of the oasis towns, the lesser clans of the Aserai still maintain their traditional nomadic lifestyle as Bedouin, raising goats and raiding the merchant caravans that ply the desert. Competition is rife in such an environment, and only the strongest clans may pull themselves out of the mire and return to civilization, wealth and power. Over a century ago, a group of these clans coalesced under the rulership of the formidable warrior Tahya, who saw that the future of his people was in the palaces and bazaars of the towns, not the saddle and by the campfire. Taking the unruly lands in the southern reaches of the Damar River from the Banu Arbas clan in a swift and bloody campaign, the people of Tahya had soon carved out a series of small emirates for themselves. When their neighboring emirs sent envoys, the self-proclaimed ‘Tahyai’ refused them, or killed the messengers outright. Now seen as heretical traitors by the rest of the Aserai, the Tahyai Emirates have since fought against their own kin, justifying their claim on the desert sands by the sword, lance and bow.">
		<relationships>
			<relationship kingdom="Kingdom.aserai"
			              value="-1"
			              isAtWar="false"/>
		</relationships>
		<policies>
			<policy id="policy_grazing_rights"/>
			<policy id="policy_council_of_elders"/>
		</policies>
	</Kingdom>
</Kingdoms>